<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>paganism on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/paganism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in paganism on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/paganism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Celtic pagan festivals</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/</guid>
      <description>The ancient Celtic pagan festivals marking important transition points during the year go back a very long time. With the coming of Wicca and neo-paganism a lot of those were appropriated and added to a new wheel of the year containing 8 festivals. When presenting these here I want to take a different approach and go back to the roots of the festivals, de-entangle them from their new age associations as much as I can and put them back into their historical and cultural context (with a focus on Irish traditions).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bealtaine</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/bealtaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/bealtaine/</guid>
      <description>Bealtaine (or Belltaine in Old Irish), which means &amp;ldquo;the month of May&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the month of the beacon-fire&amp;rdquo; is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on May 1st in the northern hemisphere. Beltane marks the first day of summer and the beginning of the pastoral season, when livestock would be driven out to their summer pastures.
Beannaich, a Thrianailt fhioir nach gann, (Bless, O Threefold true and bountiful,) Mi fein, mo cheile agus mo chlann, (Myself, my spouse and my children,) Mo chlann mhaoth&amp;rsquo;s am mathair chaomh &amp;rsquo;n an ceann, (My tender children and their beloved mother at their head,) Air chlar chubhr nan raon, air airidh chaon nam beann, (On the fragrant plain, at the gay mountain sheiling,) Air chlar chubhr nan raon, air airidh chaon nam beann.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earrach</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/earrach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/earrach/</guid>
      <description>Earrach marks the spring equinox, the balance of day and night. It is celebrated on March 20th in the northern hemisphere.
Associations Symbols:
Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fómhar</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/fomhar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/fomhar/</guid>
      <description>Fómhar marks the balance of night and day, the autumn equinox. This festival is celebrated on September 22 in the northern hemisphere. The name comes from Middle Irish fogamur‎ (&amp;ldquo;harvest&amp;rdquo;) and from Old Irish for autumn.
It is a time to mark the start of the harvest season.
Associations Symbols:
Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gheimhreadh</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/gheimhreadh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/gheimhreadh/</guid>
      <description>Gheimhreadh marks the winter solstice, the longest night of the year. It is celebrated on December 21st in the northern hemisphere.
Associations Symbols:
Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lúnasa</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/lunasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/lunasa/</guid>
      <description>Lúnasa (which means &amp;ldquo;the month of august&amp;rdquo;) is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on August 1st in the northern hemisphere. Lúnasa marks the beginning of the harvest season.
This festival is associated with the old god Lugh.
Associations Symbols: Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samhain</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhain/</guid>
      <description>Samhain (which probably comes from the Old Irish samfuin, meaning &amp;ldquo;death of Summer&amp;rdquo;) is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on October 31st in the northern hemisphere. Samhain is a feast that marks the end of the harvest and the beginning of the winter half of the year.
Samhain is one of the fire festivals, at which large bonfires were (and sometimes are still) lit. Around them, great gatherings and feasts were held in celebration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samhradh</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhradh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhradh/</guid>
      <description>Samhradh marks midsummer, the summer solstice and the longest day of the year. It is celebrated on June 20th in the northern hemisphere.
Associations Symbols: Colors: Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imbolg</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/imbolg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/imbolg/</guid>
      <description>Imbolg is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on Feburary 1st in the northern hemisphere. Imbolg is a fire festival celebrating the promise of the return of spring or the rekindling of the solar hearth.
This festival is associated with the goddess Brigid (or Bríg) who is associated with wisdom, poetry, arts and crafts, healing, protection, blacksmithing and domesticated animals. It is said that Bridgid started the custom of keening.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
