<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel log on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/travel-log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel log on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/travel-log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scotland travel log</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/travel-logs/scotland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/travel-logs/scotland/</guid>
      <description>Nature, architecture and haunted places.
The Mountains surrounding the Loch Ness Edinburgh castle from below A dirt path in a field going into a dark forest The ruins of Boleskine House Tapoch Broch Cemetery details Cemetery mushrooms </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boleskine house and burial ground</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/travel-logs/boleskine-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/travel-logs/boleskine-house/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the charred remnants of a very old and very cursed house and it&amp;rsquo;s neighbouring cemetery.
The Boleskine burial ground A faded sign marks the entrance of the cemetery Moss covered gravestones with the Loch Ness in the distance Gravestone detail The old gate lies abandoned Old monuments A strange boarded up stone house lies in a corner I step on a stone and reach in the broken window Little 666 engraved on the window frame Peaking inside, there is a fireplace with a strange occult symbold carved in the mantelpiece A trapdoor with a some ghostly dust flying around Ancient and long gone monuments General view of the burial grounds The Boleskine house Boleskine house, at least what&amp;#39;s left of it On old door frame in the ruins More doorways Glass bottle, melted by the inferno View through one of the windows More doorways The main door, partially intact A corridor filled with debris Looking out to the mountains Another corridor, this one leading to the basement stairs Stairs to the basement What&amp;#39;s left of the fireplace </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland travel log</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/iceland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/iceland/</guid>
      <description>Barren landscapes, black sand and fish bones. A journey through the harsh Icelandic winter, discovering it&amp;rsquo;s rich cultural and historical past, simple way of life and complex language.
Table of contents The city The nature The flea market The food The statue garden The history The fish drying racks Since music and the arts are running so deep in Icelandic culture (it is said jokingly by the locals that most people are at least in a band), here&amp;rsquo;s some local music to listen to while reading this travel log:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
