<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>music on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in music on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hardware</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Computing Audio Photo and video Computing Apple Macbook Pro 13&amp;quot; mid-2014 with 1TB OWC SSD drive Raspberry Pi 4B+ (I plan to turn it into a resilient computer ) Keychron K6 with green keys Audio Synths Korg Monotron MakeNoise Strega Modular synth Controllers Arturia keystep Arturia beatstep Recorders Tascam DR-40 (Really rugged and the battery lasts a long time, sadly cannot work as an audio interface and the interface isn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive) Audio players Vintage Technics cassette deck Audio Technica record player Headphones Hifiman HE350 (sound quality is good but the open back design can be annoying to others and the cord broke at some point) Photo and video I have often bought photo and video gear for specific projects or to explore new ways of making images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tapes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/tape-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/tape-collection/</guid>
      <description>Just listing all the tapes from my collection here
Table of contents Dark ambient Synth music Metal Dungeon synth Folk Dark ambient The search for the sulphurous well, Tommy Creep Rites of blood and dust, Blood and dust Sun of serpent, moone of cipher, Them Teeth Auditory witchcraft, Them Teeth Alkemisten &amp;amp; vansinnet, Them Teeth Come, deathless, Surachai Hinterpest, Mumbles Synth music Sortilèges, Potochkine Potochkine, Potochkine The devil rides out, Dream division Surlendemain acides, Autmelodi Careful, Boy Harsher Glider 10 reworks, The Sight below ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Synth Show Flyer</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-flyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-flyer/</guid>
      <description>Flyer for an underground show inspired by old-school fantasy visuals.
Flyer for an underground show </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashes of May</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/ashes-of-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/ashes-of-may/</guid>
      <description>Ashes of May by Ritual Dust A 7-min meditative drone piece that feels like taking a stroll through a field early in the morning, just in time to see the first sun rays peek at the horizon, torch in hand, on your way to light a Bealtaine bonfire.
Originally recorded for &amp;ldquo;This Trembling Place&amp;rdquo;, a drone compilation put together by fallen lo-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exsomnis</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/exsomnis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/exsomnis/</guid>
      <description>Logo and sigil for the band Exsomnis.
Exsomnis logo Sigil </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ritual Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ritual-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ritual-dust/</guid>
      <description>A series of analog-processed logos for my music project.
First version of the logo Second version of the logo Third version of the logo Detail of the texture of the logo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocal processing notes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/vocal-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/vocal-processing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Layers Effects Layers Layering vocals with more takes of the same lead (called doubles), harmonies and fills creates a much richer and fuller sound giving more energy and presence to the vocals in a track.
Doubles Doubles are two other takes of the lead melody sung in the same way with the same pitches, these are then panned all the way left and right and if needed can be chopped and ajusted to fit the rythm of the main lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inpathos EP illustrations</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/inpathos-ep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/inpathos-ep/</guid>
      <description>A series of 4 imaginary landscape paintings for the latest EP of Inpathos called ascension . I focussed on the symbolism of the places I depicted and the feeling they conjure in order to illustrate the different songs.
Painting of shores with high rocky cliffs and blue moonin the distance Painting of the snowy peak of a mountain lost in the clouds Painting of dense woods with a stream going through it, the background fading to fog Painting for the cover of the album, a mountain pass with steep cliffs and some mountains in the distance, a branch crosses the path we&amp;#39;re on and storm clouds are gathering overhead </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illuminations Album Cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/illuminations/</guid>
      <description>Painting for the cover of the second album &amp;ldquo;Illuminations&amp;rdquo; of the local dungeon synth project Aura Merlin . This second album has more of a new age, melodic ambient vibe with still some solid dungeon synth roots. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for daydreaming or pondering the deep knowledge hidden in old illuminated medieval tomes.
The arwork for it was inspired by medieval manuscripts and the illuminations that embellishes their handwritten pages. I did quite a bit of reasearch on the iconography, the colors and the gilding techniques used back in the day to make something that felt authentic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Recording</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/field-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/field-recording/</guid>
      <description>These are my personal notes and reference for field recordings. I researched and wrote those in preparation for a trip to some neolithic sites and caves in Ireland with the goal of making recordings there and using them on my upcoming album.
Microphone on a handle, connected to a small recorder Table of contents Intro to field recordings Techniques Equipment Recording Settings Data Storage Links A short intro to field recordings Field recording refers to all audio recordings performed outside of a controlled studio environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album Illustration for Andy Aquarius</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/andy-aquarius/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/andy-aquarius/</guid>
      <description>A small symbol illustration of an harp and a sword drawn for Andy Aquarius .
A small symbol illustration of an harp and a sword Symbol on the cover of the Holy Rude vinyl album </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hookups</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/the-hookups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/the-hookups/</guid>
      <description>Death metal style logo for the psych surf rock band The Hookups.
The Hookups death metal logo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voidxwitch</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/voidxwitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/voidxwitch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ok?</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/are-you-ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/are-you-ok/</guid>
      <description>Music video / ritual performance for the first song released by Voidxwitch , titled &amp;ldquo;are you ok?&amp;rdquo;. Shot in one night after a storm in rural Quebec.
We took plenty of inspiration from witchhouse and traumacore while developing visuals that are unique to Hex&amp;rsquo;s project. Most of the shots were lit with a light mounted on the camera to emulate old-school camcorders like the one used in Blair Witch, we also shot the whole thing handheld to be able to follow the movements of Hex during the performance and add some nice camera shake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Show Flyer</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-show-flyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-show-flyer/</guid>
      <description>Flyer for an underground noise show in the Mile End of Montreal which we attended as Blood and Dust.
Flyer for a noise show </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of the Repressed Poster</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-poster/</guid>
      <description>Poster design for Blood and Dust , inspired by horror movie posters. The main typography fro the title was done by hand. The photo features Hex .
Poster design for Blood and Dust Detail of the typography Detail of the photo and texture Detail of the bottom details </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixing notes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/mixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/mixing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents mixing process focussed listening midrange-focussed mixing The Mixing Process Organization Volume Panning Equalization Double checking Exporting stems Organization Tips
Group all related tracks together (drums, voice, synths, etc.) and color-code them. Name all the tracks in a way that makes it easier to find what is what. Remove all unused tracks and sounds. Volume Overall volume balancing Starting with the main tracks and working down from there, set the relative volume of the tracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOIDXWITCH</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/voidxwitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/voidxwitch/</guid>
      <description>I made this logo for VOIDXWITCH based on a scribbled text they made. The concept was to play around with some angry but childlike drawing style and the void tearing at it.
Scribbled logo in white on black Voidxwitch logo in use in their first music video </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In This Wet Place</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/orchid-lodge-album-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/orchid-lodge-album-cover/</guid>
      <description>Album cover designed for the latest Orchid Lodge album In This Wet Place , inspired by 80&amp;rsquo;s and 90&amp;rsquo;s 4AD releases.
Orchid Lodge - In This Wet Place album cover I also designed a cassette sleeve variant of this for a short-run self-published tape of the album.
Front of the cassette case and sleeve Back of the cassette case and sleeve Cassette and case Outside of the sleeve Inside of the sleeve with additional text Cassette with pad print </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ossuary Wraith</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ossuary-wraith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ossuary-wraith/</guid>
      <description>Ghastly bone-covered logo for the black metal band Ossuary Wraith
Ossuary Wraith logo Ossuary Wraith symbol </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aura Merlin</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/aura-merlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/aura-merlin/</guid>
      <description>Wizardy dungeon synth logo for Aura Merlin
Aura Merlin logo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vear</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/vear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/vear/</guid>
      <description>I made this logo for the ritual noise project Vear inspired by occult symbolism and sigils.
Logo for vear, occult-like symbols and letters overlapping each others </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Swords Album Cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/aura-merlin-3-swords/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/aura-merlin-3-swords/</guid>
      <description>Painting for the cover of the first album &amp;ldquo;Three Swords&amp;rdquo; of the local dungeon synth project Aura Merlin . The concept for the album was a lonely wanderer making their way to this cave in the woods in a quest to find three magical swords.
&amp;ldquo;Attack, threaten or defend
A gift, three swords, one choice
A passage to transcend
Through a smoky cavern, a voice..&amp;rdquo;
I was inspired by Russian landscape painters from the turn of the century for the colors and ruggedness of the trees in these kinds of snow-covered landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Folk Horror</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/folk-horror/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/folk-horror/</guid>
      <description>The sun symbol from the titles of the Wicker Man movie Table of contents Introduction Movies and television Literature Music Links Folk Horror refers to a mode of story-telling, a set of themes and to some extent an aesthetic movement fascinated by exploring the ways in which old rites, traditions and folklore can embed itself in the land and places, it digs for the ways in which humans over thousands of generations have imprinted the landscape and also how the landscape leave impressions on the human psyche.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swamp Lantern</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/swamp-lantern/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/swamp-lantern/</guid>
      <description>Mushy, heavy and psychedelic logo shrouded in thick smoke for the occult doom band Swamp Lantern .
Logo and icon Logo only Icon only </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/research/</guid>
      <description>Instruments Early music shop Irish bones McNeela Irish instruments Bodhran Music production Music Giant list of anti-fascist metal bands </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hex Ritual</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/hex-ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/hex-ritual/</guid>
      <description> All the variants of the logo and sigil Logo in black with texture Logo in white, alone Sketching process </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Synth Covers</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-covers/</guid>
      <description>Cassette sleeve designs for fictional dungeon synth albums, I&amp;rsquo;m definitely interested in making real ones so if you have a dungeon synth project and are looking for some cover art contact me!
Silent Gnome - A Contemplative Stroll Through the Castle ruins Mournful Sorcery - A Dark Conjuring of Shadows Depressive Goblin - Into the Deep Caves of Despair </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Around Your Grave I&#39;ll Light a ring of Fire</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/around-your-grave-ill-light-a-ring-of-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/around-your-grave-ill-light-a-ring-of-fire/</guid>
      <description>Cover artwork for a new single by Blood and Dust, listen to it on BandCamp here: https://blood-and-dust.bandcamp.com/track/around-your-grave-ill-light-a-ring-of-fire </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacarme Hurlant</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/vacarme-hurlant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/vacarme-hurlant/</guid>
      <description>Logo for a blackened death metal band from Quebec.
Vacarme Hurlant logo in white on black Vacarme Hurlant logo in black on white </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foulest Witch</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/foulest-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/foulest-witch/</guid>
      <description>Hand-drawn logo, sigil and illustrations for Foulest Witch, a black metal, dark ambient and ritual music label.
Complete logo with sigil and lettering Sigil Sigil with text Dagger and candleholder </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Marxen</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/nicole-marxen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/nicole-marxen/</guid>
      <description>Hand-drawn band logo for the solo project of Nicole Marxen , a mix of avant-garde pop, synthwave and experimental rock. Her first album is a meditation on grief and the painful and messy process of going through these feelings, in her own words: &amp;ldquo;I often compare the experience to uncovering a crystal, digging through foundation to discover something both jagged and brilliantly beautiful.&amp;rdquo;
Logo on a project photo Logo in grey on black </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nihtgengan</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/nihtgengan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/nihtgengan/</guid>
      <description>Hand-drawn band logo for the oniric dungeon synth / darkambient project Nihtgengan
Nihtgengan logo in white on black Nihtgengan logo in black on white </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rites of Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</guid>
      <description>Album cover and cassette sleeve design for the first Blood and Dust release. The texture used as a background to the design was photographed indoors from soil, leaves and branches collected outside and with the addition of a good amount of fake blood. The concept for this album design, especially the cassette version was to make a physical vessel to contain the music, like an ancient cursed object holding the intense emotions and energy channelled in the songs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crom Cruach</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/crom-cruach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/crom-cruach/</guid>
      <description>CROM CRUACH by Surgeryhead/Blood &amp;amp; Dust </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/crust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/crust/</guid>
      <description>CRUST Narrated by Peter Baker by Blood and Dust </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rites of Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</guid>
      <description>Rites of Blood and Dust by Blood and Dust </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodecae</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dodecae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dodecae/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Howl</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/grimhowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/grimhowl/</guid>
      <description> Grim Howl logo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood_and_dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood_and_dust/</guid>
      <description>Logo and visuals for the ritualistic horror drone project I&amp;rsquo;m doing with Hex. You can find more over on our band website: https://blood-and-dust.com/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Moth</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/curious-moth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/curious-moth/</guid>
      <description> Curious moth logo Inked logo initial sketch </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ariel</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ariel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ariel/</guid>
      <description> Ariel logo Ariel crest Ariel logo in context </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ich Hab Die Nacht Geträumet</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/ich_hab_die_nacht/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/ich_hab_die_nacht/</guid>
      <description>Credits and details Direction / Art direction: Geneviève Lamarche Reid
Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier
Singer / Actress: Viky Boyer
Shot on the Sony A6300 with a 24mm prime lens
Edited and color graded in Premiere Pro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm wishes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/warm_wishes_video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/warm_wishes_video/</guid>
      <description>Iconoclastic short video accompanied by one of my modular synth compositions, shot in slow motion with practical fire effects.
Credits Art direction / Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier-Morissette
Production Assistant: Geneviève Lamarche Reid
Model: Evey lp
Music: Haunted Attic (Devil Worship Rework) by Principe d&amp;rsquo;incertitude Shot on the Sony A6300 with a 24mm prime lens
Edited and color graded in Premiere Pro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead tongues</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/dead-tongues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/dead-tongues/</guid>
      <description>Preview video for the song Dead Tongues by Blood and dust .
Credits Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier
Assistant: Hex Evans
Shot on the Sony A6300 with a 24mm prime lens
Edited and color graded in Premiere Pro</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
