<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Saguenay travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/saguenay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/saguenay/</guid>
      <description>Hiking and climing to see the fjords, riding kids bikes down construction lanes, eating risotto as breakfast, a first escape during the plague.
The fjords of Saguenay Tall cliffs shrouded in fog Grass-roofed cabin Dying little jumping mouse on a bed of moss Mushrooms on log Hex capturing my soul A miniature moss forest in a tiny cave Looming cabins Massive lead and wood religious statue hiding behind trees Cozy spot in the woods Endless roots growing on a boulder Late evening car ride More moss Squatting forest goth Bug-eaten stump Sneaky ferns Shadow-filled woods Towering lookout Jess standing on a boulder Just enjoying the trees The creepiest track marker Empty parking lots Very pastoral traffic cone Suburban wilderness The low tide under the setting sun </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/new-orleans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/new-orleans/</guid>
      <description>Hot sauce, neon lights and plant-covered high balconies.
Tramway tracks and some mighty trees High metal-fenced balconies More beautiful trees Magazine street View from Magazine street Vintage car Frenchman street Those beed necklaces The plants just grow everywhere Architectural details Bubbles and bright colors in the sun Unexpected architecture Voodoo shop Overpass Graffiti culture is alive and well in New Orleans Famous New Orleans Po&amp;#39; Boys Pretty plant Neon signs from inside of a bar </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</guid>
      <description>Foggy alleys, crumbling buildings and the smell of beer.
Red brick alleyway at night, filled with smoke Back alleys Shawarma is a big thing here Hybrid architecture Alleyway scenes Graffiti on on old painted buildings Antique streetlight in the warm morning glow Halloween night in temple bar The well worn out stools of the local pub Some brutalist architecture Pubs in the morning The beautiful architectural mess that is Dublin A pause in the park Brutalist Dublin airport Palmtrees </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodecae</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dodecae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dodecae/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
