<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>video on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hardware</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Computing Audio Photo and video Computing Apple Macbook Pro 13&amp;quot; mid-2014 with 1TB OWC SSD drive Raspberry Pi 4B+ (I plan to turn it into a resilient computer ) Keychron K6 with green keys Audio Synths Korg Monotron MakeNoise Strega Modular synth Controllers Arturia keystep Arturia beatstep Recorders Tascam DR-40 (Really rugged and the battery lasts a long time, sadly cannot work as an audio interface and the interface isn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive) Audio players Vintage Technics cassette deck Audio Technica record player Headphones Hifiman HE350 (sound quality is good but the open back design can be annoying to others and the cord broke at some point) Photo and video I have often bought photo and video gear for specific projects or to explore new ways of making images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ok?</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/are-you-ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/are-you-ok/</guid>
      <description>Music video / ritual performance for the first song released by Voidxwitch , titled &amp;ldquo;are you ok?&amp;rdquo;. Shot in one night after a storm in rural Quebec.
We took plenty of inspiration from witchhouse and traumacore while developing visuals that are unique to Hex&amp;rsquo;s project. Most of the shots were lit with a light mounted on the camera to emulate old-school camcorders like the one used in Blair Witch, we also shot the whole thing handheld to be able to follow the movements of Hex during the performance and add some nice camera shake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ich Hab Die Nacht Geträumet</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/ich_hab_die_nacht/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/ich_hab_die_nacht/</guid>
      <description>Credits and details Direction / Art direction: Geneviève Lamarche Reid
Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier
Singer / Actress: Viky Boyer
Shot on the Sony A6300 with a 24mm prime lens
Edited and color graded in Premiere Pro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noir Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/noir_lifestyle_video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/noir_lifestyle_video/</guid>
      <description>A short film to put in moving images the lifestyle upon which Manière Noire was built. Shot mostly on location at Mont Megantic, with some interior shots done in Montreal.
Credits and details Producer: Manière Noire
Art direction: Geneviève Lamarche Reid
Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier Models: Evey lp &amp;amp; Chanel Willard
Music: Stygian by The Devil and the Universe Shot on location with the Sony A6300 and a 24mm prime lens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm wishes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/warm_wishes_video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/warm_wishes_video/</guid>
      <description>Iconoclastic short video accompanied by one of my modular synth compositions, shot in slow motion with practical fire effects.
Credits Art direction / Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier-Morissette
Production Assistant: Geneviève Lamarche Reid
Model: Evey lp
Music: Haunted Attic (Devil Worship Rework) by Principe d&amp;rsquo;incertitude Shot on the Sony A6300 with a 24mm prime lens
Edited and color graded in Premiere Pro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead tongues</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/dead-tongues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/dead-tongues/</guid>
      <description>Preview video for the song Dead Tongues by Blood and dust .
Credits Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier
Assistant: Hex Evans
Shot on the Sony A6300 with a 24mm prime lens
Edited and color graded in Premiere Pro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latency</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/latency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/video/latency/</guid>
      <description>First prototype of a never-completed short movie project about latency, absence and persistence of human presence in architecture and urban landscapes. This is all test footage shot by a one-person crew in one night in Montreal.
Credits and details Photography / Editing: Lizbeth Poirier
Music: Samuel Desrosiers Shot on the blackmagic cinema camera with a 50mm prime lens</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
