<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>magic on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/magic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in magic on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/magic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Druidism</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/druidism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/druidism/</guid>
      <description>Hand holding small boline Table of contents History Celebrations Links History of druidism Very few sources concerning the druids of the Iron age subsists to this day, most of the being accounts from Greek, Roman and christian sources. It can be interpreted from these texts that the modern image of the druid as a priestly figure presiding over sacrifices, rituals and the conservation and sharing of wisdom was mostly found amongst the druids of Gaul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magical Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/correspondences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/correspondences/</guid>
      <description>Correspondences are links between different symbolic ideas, objects, moments and ingredients. These are useful in different magical and alchemical practices to enhance the effect of a spell or ritual. I also find them useful as reference to create symbolic artworks , create sigils or to be used as a guide and tool for introspection and self-discovery.
Day correspondences Day Intent Planet Astrological sign Element Colors Deities Monday Emotions, dreams, clairvoyance Moon Cancer Water White and greys Selene, Luna, Diana, and Artemis Tuesday intent Mars Scorpio Fire Red and warm shades Mars, Ares Wednesday Communication, writing, art, creativity, mental activities Mercury Gemini, Virgo Air Yellow, grey and mixed hues Mercury, Hermes Thursday Intentions, abondance, goals, opportunities Jupiter Sagittarius, Pisces Fire Blue and purple Zeus and Thor Friday Love, friendship, emotions, beauty, sex Venus Libra, Taurus Air, Water Green, light blue, pink and copper Venus, Aphrodite Saturday Retribution, banishment, protection Saturn Capricorn Earth Black and dark shades Saturn, Hecate Sunday intent Sun Leo Fire Gold and orange Helios, Apollo, Lugh, and Bel </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planetary magic</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/planetary-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/planetary-magic/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Classical planets Modern planets Links and references The seven classical planets The Sun ☉ Representative of the ego, the self, the identity. Strong and powerful.
The modern symbol of the sun, the circumpunct, was first used during the Renaissance, it represents Apollo&amp;rsquo;s golden shield with a boss. The older medieval symbol (and alchemical symbol of gold) was a disk with a ray 🜚. In alchemy, the sun is the supreme light, the cyclical nature of the process and is associated with the conscious, energy and the ego.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Solstice 2021</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/summer-solstice-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/summer-solstice-2021/</guid>
      <description>Pausing and listening to the rhythm of the earth while the burning wheel tumbles down the hill.
A single leaf on the ground May the sun shine warm upon your face Ripples in the water A dead branch floating in water, on it&amp;#39;s cycle to fee new life A spire poking through the trees Playing the irish bones to the rhythm of the earth </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Landscape is Listening</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</guid>
      <description>Walking the urban Landscape of Montreal and noticing it&amp;rsquo;s nature, patterns and textures. Getting lost in the fragmented forest that lives beneath the city.
These photos were taken in the context of the workshop of the same name organized by Lily Hayes &amp;amp; George Saralis-Wheatley, more info can be found here: https://thelandscapeislistening.cargo.site/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrying mirror</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/scrying-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/scrying-mirror/</guid>
      <description>A mirror to look into the darkest depths. I made this scrying mirror frame out of two pieces of black-painted spruce wood tied together with waxed string - as above, so below. The pieces were carved hollow to hold the mirror without any glue - held safe but still free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Folk magic wands</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/wands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/wands/</guid>
      <description>All of my ritual tools are crafted by hand using hand tools with respect to the tree from which they came from. They are finished with natural linseed oil and wax for durability. After being completed they are cleansed over a flame. Unless specified, they are not created with a specific magical practice in mind and it is up to you to imbue them with your own personal meaning.
I am also open for custom work and commissions, feel free to reach out about those if you’re interested :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellebore zine cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/hellebore-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/hellebore-cover/</guid>
      <description>The good folks at Hellebore zine tasked me and Hex to make the cover image for their impromptu Yuletide edition . The theme was the celtic horned god, Cernunnos. With our interpretation of Cernunnos, we wanted to explore the darker aspects of the natural cycle while subverting the gender binary that is often attached to this ancient pagan divinity, channeling Cernunnos within a social and natural context that embraces nuance, complexity, and change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year Walk 2020</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/year-walk-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/year-walk-2020/</guid>
      <description>Walking on the longest night, looking inside for what&amp;rsquo;s to come.
I put on my ritual leaf crown, grabbed a lantern and ventured out in the cold empty streets and alleyways of Montreal. This was a walk I had to do alone. It was a moment I gave myself to thread new paths, going down the darkest routes without any map, open to what I could find around and inside of me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox ritual doll</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-fox/</guid>
      <description>The cunning fox escapes the hunter with its prey, crawl underneath brambles to the safety of its lair. Its power lies in its curiosity and ability to see through deceptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death ritual doll</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-death/</guid>
      <description>With his hollow ribcage, emaciated face and dark tattered robes, he is standing at the crossroads to help souls cross to the other side of the veil. This small ritual doll was crafted during the times leading up to Samhain this year, channeling the transformative energies of the dying season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Altar of inspiration</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/inspiration-altar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/inspiration-altar/</guid>
      <description>Small altar made of found and hand-made objects to inspire creativity. The little casio keyboard got a ritual burial in the making of Blood and Dust video .
Inspiration altar Inspiration altar Inspiration altar </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird walking</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/</guid>
      <description>Surreal combination of urban and natural landscape The Weird Walk zine put a name on something I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved to do, wander around cities and nature, following previously unknown paths, keeping my eyes and my mind open for new experiences and noticing weirdness when I encounter it.
I want to keep an irregular log of some of my weird walks here and add notes and references of previous weird walkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/research/</guid>
      <description>Where I keep my references for folklore, ancestry and magic research
Table of contents Folklore Ancestry Magic Folklore A website dedicated to the irish bones ancient instrument The collections of the Worcester museum The Met museum Museum of Ireland Gallica - a library of old books, manuscripts and documents The Public domain review Pictures and engravings from old books A blog on medieval woodworking A collection of horror stories in the public domain An archive of old irish documents and photographs An in-depth article about polish painted cottages A great video on wassailing The Spirit Photographs of William Hope A website on the occult sides and folkore of Paris Irish traditionnal music archive The English collections at the Pitt rivers musem London Burial Grounds Special collections of the St-Andrews University Plant lore, legends and lyrics Collection of standing stone photos A website on mudlarking on the shores of the Thames A website on misericord carvings An archive of paintings of megalithic sites Place names in reland The Beast of the Gévaudan Early Celtic art Mythical Ireland Celtic sun worship A Medieval bestiary complete guide to heraldry Website on megaliths of Ireland Ancestry Roots deeper than whiteness Magic and alchemy A very deep website on alchemichal symbolism Ambix, a publication on alchemy The Order of bards, ovates and druids An old pagan network Independent publisher of occult books Hermetic library The Museum of Witchcraft and Magic The internet sacred text archive Putressence, hermal alchemy for death rituals </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sigils and occult symbols</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/sigils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/sigils/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents What are sigils Austin Osman Spare Intuitive Sigils Word Method Rose Cross Method Planetary Square Method My own sigil work Links and References What are sigils A sigil, in it&amp;rsquo;s simplest form is a type of symbol used in a magical or ritual practice. The term sigil derives from the Latin sigillum, meaning &amp;ldquo;seal&amp;rdquo; which becomes clear when looking at the seals in the Key of Solomon for example.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
