<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in art on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Glaive of Mars</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/glaive-of-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/glaive-of-mars/</guid>
      <description>One of the magical items found in my chtonic travels, a symbolic glaive associated with the god Mars.
Pencil and acrylic on paper, 5&amp;quot; x 9&amp;quot; - 2022
Painting of a small glaive with a wolf guard, a pommel representing two snakes eating each others tails and a tip from which a flame rises Detail of the pommel with two gold snakes Detail of the tip of the glaive, coated with gold Detail of the wolf that ornates the guard </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sickle of the Sun</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-sickle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-sickle/</guid>
      <description>One of the magical items found in my chtonic travels, a symbolic sickle connected with the sun.
Pencil and acrylic on paper, 5&amp;quot; x 9&amp;quot; - 2022
Painting of a bronze sickle with a pommel featuring a solar symbol Close up of the handle, wrapped with leather strips and the pommel Detail of the tip of the blade Detail of the pencil and acrylic textures on the blade and the background </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Lock</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/vampire-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/vampire-lock/</guid>
      <description>I sculpted this vampiric lock on top of a real steel padlock and kept it functional. The inspiration for it was a drawing I made last year which you can find in my Sketchbook of December 2020 . My intent was to make something that feels old and a bit out of time and slightly threatening, something you think twice before unlocking.
The completed and painted vampiric lock We used this lock in a recent photoshoot for our band Blood and dust .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun Invocation</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-invocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-invocation/</guid>
      <description>A singular flame, borrowed from the sun, captured in paint on wood, enshrined in a sigil.
Acrylic on wood, 6&amp;quot; x 6&amp;quot; - 2021
Final painting, an oil lamp lit with a sigil to the son overlaid over it On winter solstice of this year 2021, I had the feeling that I should take painting back again, after more than 10 years. For a year now I&amp;rsquo;ve been going on personal and artistic journeys on the solstices and equinoxes, looking for insights and inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underworld I</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/underworld-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/underworld-1/</guid>
      <description>This small painting is the first in an ongoing series of depictions of chtonic travels, or katabasis, spiritual descent to the underworld in search of knowledge, lost souls or magical items.
Acrylic on wood, 6&amp;quot; x 8&amp;quot; - 2021
Small painting representing a large cave with fire coming from below it, large bonfires are lit inside of it surrounded by tiny figures Detail of the lower part of the painting, showing a ledge, some rising smoke and fire Extreme close up of the painting showing tiny figures with torches assembled around a bonfire Details of the ceiling of the cave, covered with stalactites </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolism in art</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/symbolism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/symbolism/</guid>
      <description>The Three Fates by Alexander Rothaug Table of contents Overview and themes Notable artists Overview and themes Symbolism was a literary and visual art movement from the late 19th century of French, Russian and Belgian origins. Literature, myth religion and poetry are it&amp;rsquo;s main sources of inspiration material, with artists drawing from old mythology, medieval poetry and more modern pieces like Les Fleurs du Mal from Charles Baudelaire as inspiration for visual pieces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ariel Doom</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ariel-doom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/ariel-doom/</guid>
      <description>A lettering piece made for the black metal-themed art project of a friend, see more over on her instagram .
Ariel Doom logo in white on black Ariel Doom logo in black on white </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Moth</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/curious-moth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/curious-moth/</guid>
      <description> Curious moth logo Inked logo initial sketch </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
