<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ashes of May</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/ashes-of-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/ashes-of-may/</guid>
      <description>Ashes of May by Ritual Dust A 7-min meditative drone piece that feels like taking a stroll through a field early in the morning, just in time to see the first sun rays peek at the horizon, torch in hand, on your way to light a Bealtaine bonfire.
Originally recorded for &amp;ldquo;This Trembling Place&amp;rdquo;, a drone compilation put together by fallen lo-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocal processing notes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/vocal-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/vocal-processing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Layers Effects Layers Layering vocals with more takes of the same lead (called doubles), harmonies and fills creates a much richer and fuller sound giving more energy and presence to the vocals in a track.
Doubles Doubles are two other takes of the lead melody sung in the same way with the same pitches, these are then panned all the way left and right and if needed can be chopped and ajusted to fit the rythm of the main lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Recording</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/field-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/field-recording/</guid>
      <description>These are my personal notes and reference for field recordings. I researched and wrote those in preparation for a trip to some neolithic sites and caves in Ireland with the goal of making recordings there and using them on my upcoming album.
Microphone on a handle, connected to a small recorder Table of contents Intro to field recordings Techniques Equipment Recording Settings Data Storage Links A short intro to field recordings Field recording refers to all audio recordings performed outside of a controlled studio environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixing notes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/mixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/mixing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents mixing process focussed listening midrange-focussed mixing The Mixing Process Organization Volume Panning Equalization Double checking Exporting stems Organization Tips
Group all related tracks together (drums, voice, synths, etc.) and color-code them. Name all the tracks in a way that makes it easier to find what is what. Remove all unused tracks and sounds. Volume Overall volume balancing Starting with the main tracks and working down from there, set the relative volume of the tracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/research/</guid>
      <description>Instruments Early music shop Irish bones McNeela Irish instruments Bodhran Music production Music Giant list of anti-fascist metal bands </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crom Cruach</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/crom-cruach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/crom-cruach/</guid>
      <description>CROM CRUACH by Surgeryhead/Blood &amp;amp; Dust </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/crust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/crust/</guid>
      <description>CRUST Narrated by Peter Baker by Blood and Dust </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rites of Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</guid>
      <description>Rites of Blood and Dust by Blood and Dust </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
