<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>urban on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/urban/</link>
    <description>Recent content in urban on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/urban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Failed utopia</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/failed-utopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/failed-utopia/</guid>
      <description>Brutalist ruins of Montreal&amp;rsquo;s olympic stadium and surrounding public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</guid>
      <description>Foggy alleys, crumbling buildings and the smell of beer.
Red brick alleyway at night, filled with smoke Back alleys Shawarma is a big thing here Hybrid architecture Alleyway scenes Graffiti on on old painted buildings Antique streetlight in the warm morning glow Halloween night in temple bar The well worn out stools of the local pub Some brutalist architecture Pubs in the morning The beautiful architectural mess that is Dublin A pause in the park Brutalist Dublin airport Palmtrees </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban unease</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/suburban-unease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/suburban-unease/</guid>
      <description>A series of cinematic shots of the Montreal suburbs trying to capture the feeling of unease, distrust and inhospitality of higher middle class white neighbourhoods.
Entering a shadowy backyard A mysterious hole in the ground filled with concrete debris Empty windows looming, covered in vine Perfect spot to peak at passerbys through the blinds and the overgrown bushes Windows like empty eyes trapped behind fences The local church Houses built like an overprotective parent with a gaping mouth as a door Little signs letting you that there&amp;#39;s always someone watching Who knows what happens behind closed (garage) doors </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smothered</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/smothered/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/smothered/</guid>
      <description>A heavy white blanket swallowing the city.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
