<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rock drawings</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/rock-drawings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/rock-drawings/</guid>
      <description>Ephemeral rock drawings done in different locations and times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To the otherworld</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/to-the-otherworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/to-the-otherworld/</guid>
      <description>The fifth of my monthly print club
Linocut on paper, 4.5&amp;quot; x 10&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust To the otherworld limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 28, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD
Add to cart </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decay</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/decay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/decay/</guid>
      <description>The forth of my monthly print club, is complementary to the first one, decay and growth working together in an endless cycle, just in time for the coming of death season.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Decay limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 28, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Henbane</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/henbane/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/henbane/</guid>
      <description>The third print of my monthly print club, a henbane plant, one of the psychoactive plants used by witches in their flying ointment.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Henbane limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 24, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hekate</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/hekate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/hekate/</guid>
      <description>Second print of my monthly print club, the key to the underworld and the snake, two symbols of Hekate, the goddess of boundaries, the underworld and witchcraft.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Hekate limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 30, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/growth/</guid>
      <description>First print of my monthly print club, a mushroom growing from a hand, a piece about growth and connection with the self and what surrounds us.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Become a stone circle patron to join the monthly print club and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Growth limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 20, numbered and stamped with my seal, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glaive of Mars</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/glaive-of-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/glaive-of-mars/</guid>
      <description>One of the magical items found in my chtonic travels, a symbolic glaive associated with the god Mars.
Pencil and acrylic on paper, 5&amp;quot; x 9&amp;quot; - 2022
Painting of a small glaive with a wolf guard, a pommel representing two snakes eating each others tails and a tip from which a flame rises Detail of the pommel with two gold snakes Detail of the tip of the glaive, coated with gold Detail of the wolf that ornates the guard </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sickle of the Sun</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-sickle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-sickle/</guid>
      <description>One of the magical items found in my chtonic travels, a symbolic sickle connected with the sun.
Pencil and acrylic on paper, 5&amp;quot; x 9&amp;quot; - 2022
Painting of a bronze sickle with a pommel featuring a solar symbol Close up of the handle, wrapped with leather strips and the pommel Detail of the tip of the blade Detail of the pencil and acrylic textures on the blade and the background </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun Invocation</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-invocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/sun-invocation/</guid>
      <description>A singular flame, borrowed from the sun, captured in paint on wood, enshrined in a sigil.
Acrylic on wood, 6&amp;quot; x 6&amp;quot; - 2021
Final painting, an oil lamp lit with a sigil to the son overlaid over it On winter solstice of this year 2021, I had the feeling that I should take painting back again, after more than 10 years. For a year now I&amp;rsquo;ve been going on personal and artistic journeys on the solstices and equinoxes, looking for insights and inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underworld I</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/underworld-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/underworld-1/</guid>
      <description>This small painting is the first in an ongoing series of depictions of chtonic travels, or katabasis, spiritual descent to the underworld in search of knowledge, lost souls or magical items.
Acrylic on wood, 6&amp;quot; x 8&amp;quot; - 2021
Small painting representing a large cave with fire coming from below it, large bonfires are lit inside of it surrounded by tiny figures Detail of the lower part of the painting, showing a ledge, some rising smoke and fire Extreme close up of the painting showing tiny figures with torches assembled around a bonfire Details of the ceiling of the cave, covered with stalactites </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal artifacts</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/personal-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/personal-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>This ongoing series documents my personal collections of artifacts, some with historical significance, some purely some stick or rock found in the woods somewhere, but all with meaning and a past of future story attached to them. In archeology, artifacts are only as precious as their well-documented provenance and context that allows them to tell a more complete story. These items that I found, unearthed or bought have a story of their own but also a story that I made for them, this is an exercise in collecting those stories so they can be shared and hopefully inspire other people to create stories of their own for their favourite found objects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Landscape is Listening</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</guid>
      <description>Walking the urban Landscape of Montreal and noticing it&amp;rsquo;s nature, patterns and textures. Getting lost in the fragmented forest that lives beneath the city.
These photos were taken in the context of the workshop of the same name organized by Lily Hayes &amp;amp; George Saralis-Wheatley, more info can be found here: https://thelandscapeislistening.cargo.site/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heavy black veil</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/veil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/veil/</guid>
      <description>Darkness hides what was obvious to better reveal what was occulted</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
