<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zine on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/zine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in zine on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/zine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fant么mes issue 2 cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/fantomes-2-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/fantomes-2-cover/</guid>
      <description>Pen and ink illustration of a gothic cemetery scene for the upcoming 2nd issue of my ghost story and haunting images zine Fant么mes .
Pen and ink illustration of a cemetery with a large iron gate, a lantern on one of the gate pillars, plenty of tombstones in the distance and a victorian house in the distance Illustration in context on the cover of the zine with some text on the back and the logo on the front </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fant么mes Zine - issue 1</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/fantomes-zine-issue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/fantomes-zine-issue-1/</guid>
      <description>Fant么mes was my first zine project, one that started very small when I realized that I could regroup in a zine my obsession with ghosts, the drawings I made of them and the photos of ghostly places I took. Then I asked around to see if other people would be interested in creating or writing pieces about ghosts, and got an incredible response. I then spent the next 6 months collecting, assembling, laying out and illustrating all that material to form what became the first issue of this little zine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellebore zine cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/hellebore-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/hellebore-cover/</guid>
      <description>The good folks at Hellebore zine tasked me and Hex to make the cover image for their impromptu Yuletide edition . The theme was the celtic horned god, Cernunnos. With our interpretation of Cernunnos, we wanted to explore the darker aspects of the natural cycle while subverting the gender binary that is often attached to this ancient pagan divinity, channeling Cernunnos within a social and natural context that embraces nuance, complexity, and change.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
