<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cemetery on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/cemetery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cemetery on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/cemetery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cemetery Walk Samhain 2022</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-samhain-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-samhain-2022/</guid>
      <description>On the eve of Samhain we ventured out at the end of the day to go visit the ruin of the Calvin Presbyterian Church and it&amp;rsquo;s cemetery in the small rural town of Saint-Anicet in Quebec. The whole place was surprisingly well maintained (compared to how it looked in 2002) and contained a wealth of ancient tombstones.
The church was once part of a settlement comprised of people with French, Irish, and Scottish heritage called Godmanchester Village created in the 1820&amp;rsquo;s which only survived around 30 years and was then abandoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cemetery Walk October 2022</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-oct-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-oct-2022/</guid>
      <description> A collapsing crypt A mystery bone Leaf-covered steps A mysterious figure walking towards the horizon Me standing in an archway An abandoned spiderweb Mysterious figure amongst the graves The sun shining through the leaves Colors turning in the canopy A lonely wooden cross Hex squatting in the long grass Broken cross on the long grass Hex lying down amongst the forgotten Me enjoying the warm sun Another lonely cross Me with some trees in the background </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
