<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sweet on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/sweet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sweet on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/sweet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bonbons aux patates</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/bonbons-aux-patates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/bonbons-aux-patates/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 small potato 3 cups powdered sugar 1 tsp of vegan butter 1/2 tsp of vanilla extract 4 tbsp of peanut butter Steps Boil 1 small potato in water until it is soft when poked with a fork, around 15 min Let the potato cool, when it is safe to handle, remove its skin and put in large mixing bowl Add 1 tsp of vegan butter and 1/2 tsp of vanilla extract to the potato and mash very well until there is no more clumps Add 3 cups powdered sugar to the potato mixture in small batches while mixing together, it should create a semi-firm dough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple crisp oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/apple-crisp-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/apple-crisp-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of rolled oats 1 cup of water 2 tbsp of plant-based milk 2 tbsp of brown sugar half an apple or 2 tbsp of applesauce 1/2 tsp of plant-based butter (if using apples) small handful of granola 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp cloves 1/4 tsp nutmeg Steps If using apples, cut half an apple in small squares and put in a pan with 1/2 tsp of plant-based butter, cook until sligthly browned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wassail</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/wassail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/wassail/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 large baking apples, peeled and cored 4 cups of ale, beer or cider (alcohol free if desired) 1/2 cup of sugar 1 cinnamon stick, broken in half, or 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1 teaspoon ground ginger zest of 1 lemon Steps Pre-heat your oven to 400°F, cut 3 large baking apples in thick slices and arrange them in a baking dish, sprinkle a bit of sugar on top.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matcha and spirulina latte</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/matcha-spirulina-latte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/matcha-spirulina-latte/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup of plant-based milk 1 tsp of spirulina 2 tsp of matcha powder 1 tbsp of raw sugar (optional) Steps In a small pot combine 1 cup of plant-based milk, 1 tsp of spirulina, 2 tsp of matcha powder and 1 tbsp of raw sugar (if adding it) Cook on medium/high until it starts smoking while continuously whisking it, around 5 min. Turn off the heat and transfer to a mug, enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/winter-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/winter-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats 1 cup of water 2 tbsp of plant-based milk 2 tbsp of brown sugar 2 tbsp of dried cranberries 1/4 tsp of vanilla 6 - 8 entire pecans 1/4 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp cardamom 1/4 tsp cloves 1/4 tsp nutmeg Steps In a small pot combine 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats and 1 cup of water Cook on medium/high until it boils, around 7 min while stirring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/fall-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/fall-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats 1 cup of water 2 tbsp of plant-based milk 2 tbsp of brown sugar pumpkin purée dark chocolate chips pumpkin seeds 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp powdered ginger 1/4 tsp nutmeg Steps In a small pot combine 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats and 1 cup of water Cook on medium/high until it boils, around 7 min while stirring. Turn of the heat and add 2 tbsp of plant-based milk, mix well.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
