<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>notes on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in notes on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Way of life</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/way-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/way-of-life/</guid>
      <description>This is in no way intended to be general advice or universal truth, it&amp;rsquo;s what worked for me in life so far. These are the result of a long distillation process, introspection, life experiences, therapy and meditation. It will definitely change in the future, like myself. It is written in that form as a message from present me to future me.
Table of contents Listen to nature Know your feelings Trust your body Set boundaries Take accountability Practice gratitude Learn your privilege Tend to your insecurities Be honest with yourself Commitments not tasks Cultivate a relationship with nature Nature is always there somewhere, even in the most brutalist city corners and we&amp;rsquo;re part of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ghost is part of the earth now</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/the-ghost-is-part-of-the-earth-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/the-ghost-is-part-of-the-earth-now/</guid>
      <description>I no more feel like a ghost, i feel like the earth, the soil with it’s deep and complex network of roots and mycelium, with a whole ecosystem of bugs and living things crawling around. I can feel the cover of dead leaves and rotting fruit accumulated on top of me, not hindering my feelings but comforting like a blanket, protecting the bulbs and the nuts that fell on the ground at the turn of the seasons, allowing them to slowly get ready to bloom in the spring, feeding on this bed of decomposing remnants from the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Druidism</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/druidism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/druidism/</guid>
      <description>Hand holding small boline Table of contents History Celebrations Links History of druidism Very few sources concerning the druids of the Iron age subsists to this day, most of the being accounts from Greek, Roman and christian sources. It can be interpreted from these texts that the modern image of the druid as a priestly figure presiding over sacrifices, rituals and the conservation and sharing of wisdom was mostly found amongst the druids of Gaul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On being trans</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/being-trans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/being-trans/</guid>
      <description>I am powerful, fierce, resourceful, creative, weird, caring. I am so much more and also none of that, in my own way. I take some time here to write about womxnhood and encourage everyone to actively challenge how we perceive it. Let the womxn in your life expand your definition of it.
It’s been an incredible journey getting to know the trans womxn I am and coming to terms with how I want to live my life from this point forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Computing Audio Photo and video Computing Apple Macbook Pro 13&amp;quot; mid-2014 with 1TB OWC SSD drive Raspberry Pi 4B+ (I plan to turn it into a resilient computer ) Keychron K6 with green keys Audio Synths Korg Monotron MakeNoise Strega Modular synth Controllers Arturia keystep Arturia beatstep Recorders Tascam DR-40 (Really rugged and the battery lasts a long time, sadly cannot work as an audio interface and the interface isn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive) Audio players Vintage Technics cassette deck Audio Technica record player Headphones Hifiman HE350 (sound quality is good but the open back design can be annoying to others and the cord broke at some point) Photo and video I have often bought photo and video gear for specific projects or to explore new ways of making images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/software/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Visual tools Audio tools Coding tools Utilities Links Software tools for me are mostly a mean to an end, although I do enjoy building them if I have a specific problem and nothing is available that I find simple and efficient enough for the task. I&amp;rsquo;m currently migrating away from proprietary tools towards open source tools compatible with a wider range of OSes and that could run on my resilient computer .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking grains and cereals</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/cooking-grains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/cooking-grains/</guid>
      <description>Rolled oats 2 cups of water for every cup of oats.
Combine the oats and water in a pot. Bring to a boil, then reduce to medium heat, let cook for 15 minutes. Steel-cut oats 3 1/2 to 4 cups water for every cup of oats.
Combine the oats and water in a pot. Bring to a boil, then reduce to medium heat, let cook for 20 minutes while stirring from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom album cover illustration</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/custom-album-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/custom-album-cover/</guid>
      <description>Album covers I can do album covers in pencil, as an acrylic painting or with processed photography. In all cases, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the concept of the album, its themes, and how they should be represented visually. From there, if we go with illustration or painting I&amp;rsquo;ll do sketches, a round of adjustments and complete the final piece. Please note that I only do things that fit my illustration style ( see here for reference ).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocal processing notes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/vocal-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/vocal-processing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Layers Effects Layers Layering vocals with more takes of the same lead (called doubles), harmonies and fills creates a much richer and fuller sound giving more energy and presence to the vocals in a track.
Doubles Doubles are two other takes of the lead melody sung in the same way with the same pitches, these are then panned all the way left and right and if needed can be chopped and ajusted to fit the rythm of the main lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Recording</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/field-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/field-recording/</guid>
      <description>These are my personal notes and reference for field recordings. I researched and wrote those in preparation for a trip to some neolithic sites and caves in Ireland with the goal of making recordings there and using them on my upcoming album.
Microphone on a handle, connected to a small recorder Table of contents Intro to field recordings Techniques Equipment Recording Settings Data Storage Links A short intro to field recordings Field recording refers to all audio recordings performed outside of a controlled studio environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom lettering work</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/commissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/commissions/</guid>
      <description>Band / Project logo I have quite a bit of experience doing lettering work and logos for bands of a good range of genres but mostly black metal, doom, dungeon synth, noise and experimental music.
When you commission me a logo, the first step is talking a bit more with you about what you’re envisioning and getting any inspirations that you like as a reference point (you can also just give me wildcard and I’ll work from the music and the name itself).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bealtaine</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/bealtaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/bealtaine/</guid>
      <description>Bealtaine (or Belltaine in Old Irish), which means &amp;ldquo;the month of May&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the month of the beacon-fire&amp;rdquo; is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on May 1st in the northern hemisphere. Beltane marks the first day of summer and the beginning of the pastoral season, when livestock would be driven out to their summer pastures.
Beannaich, a Thrianailt fhioir nach gann, (Bless, O Threefold true and bountiful,) Mi fein, mo cheile agus mo chlann, (Myself, my spouse and my children,) Mo chlann mhaoth&amp;rsquo;s am mathair chaomh &amp;rsquo;n an ceann, (My tender children and their beloved mother at their head,) Air chlar chubhr nan raon, air airidh chaon nam beann, (On the fragrant plain, at the gay mountain sheiling,) Air chlar chubhr nan raon, air airidh chaon nam beann.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earrach</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/earrach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/earrach/</guid>
      <description>Earrach marks the spring equinox, the balance of day and night. It is celebrated on March 20th in the northern hemisphere.
Associations Symbols:
Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fómhar</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/fomhar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/fomhar/</guid>
      <description>Fómhar marks the balance of night and day, the autumn equinox. This festival is celebrated on September 22 in the northern hemisphere. The name comes from Middle Irish fogamur‎ (&amp;ldquo;harvest&amp;rdquo;) and from Old Irish for autumn.
It is a time to mark the start of the harvest season.
Associations Symbols:
Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gheimhreadh</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/gheimhreadh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/gheimhreadh/</guid>
      <description>Gheimhreadh marks the winter solstice, the longest night of the year. It is celebrated on December 21st in the northern hemisphere.
Associations Symbols:
Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lúnasa</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/lunasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/lunasa/</guid>
      <description>Lúnasa (which means &amp;ldquo;the month of august&amp;rdquo;) is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on August 1st in the northern hemisphere. Lúnasa marks the beginning of the harvest season.
This festival is associated with the old god Lugh.
Associations Symbols: Colors:
Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samhain</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhain/</guid>
      <description>Samhain (which probably comes from the Old Irish samfuin, meaning &amp;ldquo;death of Summer&amp;rdquo;) is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on October 31st in the northern hemisphere. Samhain is a feast that marks the end of the harvest and the beginning of the winter half of the year.
Samhain is one of the fire festivals, at which large bonfires were (and sometimes are still) lit. Around them, great gatherings and feasts were held in celebration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samhradh</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhradh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/samhradh/</guid>
      <description>Samhradh marks midsummer, the summer solstice and the longest day of the year. It is celebrated on June 20th in the northern hemisphere.
Associations Symbols: Colors: Herbs and plants:
Trees:
Links and references </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cottage restoration</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/cottage-restoration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/cottage-restoration/</guid>
      <description>Derelict cottage in the Irish landscape Table of contents Glossary Finding a cottage Inspection and survey Planning Walls Floors Roof Windows and doors Heating Resources I&amp;rsquo;m building this page to collect my notes, research and resources on the restoration of traditional Irish cottages. It is a project I&amp;rsquo;m planning to do with some help in the future when we move to Ireland so I&amp;rsquo;m doing a lot of prep and research work in advance to be ready when we get to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for your tattoo session</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/before-session-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/before-session-prep/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents The week before The day before The day of The week before Drink plenty of water and stay hydrated, this will help your skin be in better condition for tattooing and heal better. Moisturize your skin regularly to keep it in its optimal condition.
The day before Shave the general area where you want your tattoo while being careful not to break or cut the skin since damaged skin cannot be tattooed and has to heal before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom tattoo project form</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/tattoo-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/tattoo-form/</guid>
      <description>Fill this form if you have an idea for a custom tattoo that you&amp;rsquo;d like to have done by me. When you&amp;rsquo;ve completed it, hit the submit button and then send the email that it will generate for you. I will answer your request by email at the address you provide as soon as possible.
About you First name (required) Last name (required) Preferred name Pronouns She/Her He/Him They/Them Ze/Zir Would prefer by name Birthdate (required) Email (required) Phone number About your project What subject matter apply to your tattoo?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixing notes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/mixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/mixing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents mixing process focussed listening midrange-focussed mixing The Mixing Process Organization Volume Panning Equalization Double checking Exporting stems Organization Tips
Group all related tracks together (drums, voice, synths, etc.) and color-code them. Name all the tracks in a way that makes it easier to find what is what. Remove all unused tracks and sounds. Volume Overall volume balancing Starting with the main tracks and working down from there, set the relative volume of the tracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witches Flying Ointment</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/witches-flying-ointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/witches-flying-ointment/</guid>
      <description>Flying ointment or salve is a potentially hallucinogenic and highly toxic blend of plants in a fatty base that appears in folklore, fiction and books relating to witch hunting dating back to the middle ages. There&amp;rsquo;s still quite a bit of debate amongst folklorists and researchers on whether such ointments actually existed, if they actually contained the toxic and hallucinogenic plants often associated with them and whether they are one of the sources of the myth of the witch flying on a broom (the theory being that witches would craft mind-altering flying ointment, apply it on a broom stick and &amp;ldquo;ride&amp;rdquo; it in order to &amp;ldquo;fly&amp;rdquo;, in a combination of sexual stimulation, trance state and possibly vivid dreams and visions of flying).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo station setup</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tattoo-station-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tattoo-station-setup/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Setup Teardown Green soap recipe Setup Step 1: setup surface Wash your hands Put on gloves Spray top of station with water or alcohol Cover top of station with plastic film, leaving some overhanging Cover power supply with bag Tape a dental bib on top of station Step 2: prepare supplies If making a large tattoo or one with a lot of a color of ink it&#39;s best to take out more ink cups and fill them than having to refill during the tattoo Take out these supplies and lay them on the station: new disposable razor machine bag (cut a corner) disposable grip (drop without touching) clip cord bag (only touch ends) wash bottle bag rubber nipple ink caps small strip of tape enough strips of paper towels for the tattoo Cover green soap bottle with a bottle bag, while touching the outside of the plastic as little as possible, making sure to cover the bottom, then put it on the station Using a wooden stick, scoop some vaseline and then using the other side scoop some shea butter (or other tattooing lotion), then put the vaseline on the top of station to hold the stick in place and stick it in in with the vaseline and lotion on top Get your ink caps out, dip the bottom of them in vaseline and stick them to the wooden stick Get the needles that you&amp;rsquo;ll need for the tattoo out and put them on the station Step 3: prepare machine Keep the machine and clip cord on the tattoo bed until they are fully bagged to prevent cross-contamination of the clean station Slide clip cord in clip cord bag while touching the bag as little as possible, protect part of clip cord closest to the machine Plug clip cord in power supply and keep the other end covered with the bag on the station Take the disposable grip and slide the tube part through the small hole in the machine bag, then reverse the bag on your hand and the grip Grab your machine and attach it to the grip, then pull back the machine bag on the machine Plug the clip cord in the machine and tape the machine bag close, now you can put the machine on the station step 4: prepare tattoo bed Once everything is off the tattoo bed, spray it with medical disinfectant and leave it on for the maximum kill time Wrap the area where the tattooed body part if gonna be, plus a bit larger with plastic film If using an arm rest, clean it and cover it with plastic film too Step 5: Prepare and apply stencil Step 6: pour ink Once the stencil is applied and drying, put a new set of gloves Shake your ink and pour it in the ink cup and get ready for tattooing Teardown Wash your hands and put on gloves Remove needle from grip, put all needles in needle disposal container Remove the plastic covering the tattoo bed without touching the top surface, wrap it in a ball and throw it away Remove grip from machine and leave it on the station Drop machine and cable out of plastic on the tattoo bed, leave the bags on the station drop the wash bottle out of its bag onto the bed without touching it and leave the bag on the station Wrap all the stuff on the station in the plastic without touching the top surface and throw it away, removing your gloves at the same time Put on a new pair of gloves Spray the tattoo bed, station top, machine, wash bottle, clip cord and power supply with medical disinfectant and leave on for the maximum length of the kill time Green soap recipe In a 16 oz wash bottle mix the pure green soap with distilled water in a ration of 1 part green soap for 8 parts water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo stencil</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tattoo-stencil-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tattoo-stencil-application/</guid>
      <description> Table of contents find size Copy stencil Prep skin Apply stencil Step 1: Find design size Print the design in black and white in a size that seems good for the placement Cut around the printed design and try it on the body of the client, making sure the size is good If needed, resize with the printer, print again and double check the new size Step 2: Copy stencil by hand Once the good size was found, get a sheet of stencil paper and remove the tissue paper barrier Tape the printed design on top of the stencil paper to prevent it from moving Using a ballpoint pen, trace over the lines of the design while applying good pressure Before removing the design, make sure all the lines are copied Remove the taped design and cut the stencil to size Place it onto the tattoo bed, stencil side up Step 2: Copy stencil with a thermal stencil machine Once the good size was found, tape the design on a blank sheet of paper, leaving some room at the bottom Get a sheet of stencil paper and remove the tissue paper barrier Place the stencil paper in the machine Place the sheet with the design in the machine Press copy and hold the stencil paper with both hands slowly pulling on it while it copies the design Once the copy is done cut around the stencil and place it onto the tattoo bed, stencil side up Step 3: Prep skin Wash your hands and put on some gloves Take your razor and shave very closely the area you&amp;rsquo;re gonna tattoo + around 2 inches After the skin is shaved, use an alcohol pad or prep stuff to sterilize the skin Step 4: Apply stencil Once the alcohol has dried, apply a moderately generous amount of stencil stuff to the area, spreading it with your finger to get an even thin coat Hold the stencil over the area and when really sure of placement apply it onto the skin starting from the middle Slowly stick the rest of the stencil to the skin with your finger working from the middle towards the outside Rub it slightly when it&amp;rsquo;s all stuck to the skin Slowly peel the stencil off Leave to dry for around 10 minutes </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Available flash</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/flash/</guid>
      <description>Dark Fantasy An ongoing series of pieces inspired by old-school DnD, dark fantasy and sword and sorcery. All pieces 6&amp;quot; minimum except the ones labelled small.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 (small) 15 16 (small) 17 18 19 (small) 20 21 22 (small) 23 24 25 Fear the old blood Ongoing series of flashes inspired by the blood-soaked streets of Yarnham and their underlying eldritch horrors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Civilization Anarchism</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/anarchism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/anarchism/</guid>
      <description>Post Civilization is an idea that I&amp;rsquo;ve first encountered when I was about 18, still in university, very much a self-described anarchist and at the time quite active in the student movements. Revisiting this idea of a way of living post-civilization that is more sustainable, more equal and more fulfilling still rings true 14 years later with the current climate crisis and the constant train wreck of late-stage capitalism.
The first iteration of that philosophy comes from a small zine published by Strangers In a Tangled Wilderness called Post-Civ!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo aftercare</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/aftercare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/tattoo/aftercare/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Aftercare routine Recommended products Stages of tattoo healing Placements that need extra care Signs of infection Links Aftercare routine With specialized film (Saniderm) Day 1 Keep the specialized tattoo film on your tattoo first the first 24h. Day 2 If your tattoo artist gave you extra sheets of tattoo film, remove the tattoo film and clean the tattoo gently using your fingers with a mild antibacterial soap, pat dry with a paper towel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agroecology and Rewilding</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/agroecology/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/agroecology/</guid>
      <description>Small stream with native plants and logs Table of contents Introduction Concrete examples Links Introduction There&amp;rsquo;s no mystery that our relationship to nature and the way ecosystems work has shifted dramatically over time, basically almost from the time we started large scale cultivation of crops. Things got further aggravated during colonization with the import of exotic plants, animals and bugs that disrupted the existing relationships and balance present in the native ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Folk Horror</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/folk-horror/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/folk-horror/</guid>
      <description>The sun symbol from the titles of the Wicker Man movie Table of contents Introduction Movies and television Literature Music Links Folk Horror refers to a mode of story-telling, a set of themes and to some extent an aesthetic movement fascinated by exploring the ways in which old rites, traditions and folklore can embed itself in the land and places, it digs for the ways in which humans over thousands of generations have imprinted the landscape and also how the landscape leave impressions on the human psyche.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imbolg</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/imbolg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/festivals/imbolg/</guid>
      <description>Imbolg is an ancient Celtic festival and celebration that takes place on Feburary 1st in the northern hemisphere. Imbolg is a fire festival celebrating the promise of the return of spring or the rekindling of the solar hearth.
This festival is associated with the goddess Brigid (or Bríg) who is associated with wisdom, poetry, arts and crafts, healing, protection, blacksmithing and domesticated animals. It is said that Bridgid started the custom of keening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/music/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/music/research/</guid>
      <description>Instruments Early music shop Irish bones McNeela Irish instruments Bodhran Music production Music Giant list of anti-fascist metal bands </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favourite recipes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/favorite-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/favorite-recipes/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Breakfast Sides Pasta Stews Soups Comfort food Sandwiches Desserts Bread Breakfast Vegan buttermilk pancakes Date bread Latkes Sides Kimchi Lembas Grilled brussels sprouts Potato salad Pasta Creamy mushroom pasta Cauliflower mushroom pasta bake Butternut squash pasta Gochujang mushroom pasta Alfredo truffle pasta Tuscan gnocchi Tuna casserole Peanut tofu noodle bowls Mushroom pasta Soba noodles carbonara noodles Stews Southern fried cabbage Japanese curry Spicy vegetable stew Spanish rice with chickpeas Moroccan Tagine Dublin Coddle Soups Zuppa toscana Coconut Curry soup Creamy mushroom ramen Potato and leek soup Broccoli and cheese soup Salads Roasted carrots and chickpea salad Comfort food Lasagna Curry mac and cheese Tofu ribs Cauliflower buffalo wings Spanakopita Wellington Mushroom quesadillas Loaded baked potatoes Cauliflower and butternut squash gratin Mushroom lentil loaf Corn Pone Hard tacos with beyond meat Lentils and mushrooms on mashed potatoes Quiche Fish and chips Mexican rice shepherd&amp;#39;s pie Sandwiches Tempeh Reuben Sandwich Banh mi Jerk wrap Chicken ceasar wrap Desserts Depression cake Cinnamon rolls Brownies Banana bread Fruit cake Tofu chocolate mousse Pumpkin cake Butternut squash pudding Cinnamon rolls Welsh cakes Oatmeal raisin cookies Peanut butter cookies Choco chips cookies Gingersnaps Vegan cheese Cashew camembert Vegan camembert cheese making supplies Sauces Marinara sauce Mushroom ketchup Peanut sauce Alfredo Sauce Dips and butters Vegan nutella Bread Sourdough starter Breakfast sausage bread Borodinski bread </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magical Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/correspondences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/correspondences/</guid>
      <description>Correspondences are links between different symbolic ideas, objects, moments and ingredients. These are useful in different magical and alchemical practices to enhance the effect of a spell or ritual. I also find them useful as reference to create symbolic artworks , create sigils or to be used as a guide and tool for introspection and self-discovery.
Day correspondences Day Intent Planet Astrological sign Element Colors Deities Monday Emotions, dreams, clairvoyance Moon Cancer Water White and greys Selene, Luna, Diana, and Artemis Tuesday intent Mars Scorpio Fire Red and warm shades Mars, Ares Wednesday Communication, writing, art, creativity, mental activities Mercury Gemini, Virgo Air Yellow, grey and mixed hues Mercury, Hermes Thursday Intentions, abondance, goals, opportunities Jupiter Sagittarius, Pisces Fire Blue and purple Zeus and Thor Friday Love, friendship, emotions, beauty, sex Venus Libra, Taurus Air, Water Green, light blue, pink and copper Venus, Aphrodite Saturday Retribution, banishment, protection Saturn Capricorn Earth Black and dark shades Saturn, Hecate Sunday intent Sun Leo Fire Gold and orange Helios, Apollo, Lugh, and Bel </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planetary magic</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/planetary-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/planetary-magic/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Classical planets Modern planets Links and references The seven classical planets The Sun ☉ Representative of the ego, the self, the identity. Strong and powerful.
The modern symbol of the sun, the circumpunct, was first used during the Renaissance, it represents Apollo&amp;rsquo;s golden shield with a boss. The older medieval symbol (and alchemical symbol of gold) was a disk with a ray 🜚. In alchemy, the sun is the supreme light, the cyclical nature of the process and is associated with the conscious, energy and the ego.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/research/</guid>
      <description>References, archives and research material on illustration and art
Table of contents Essays and interviews Archives References Essays and interviews Interview – Denis Forkas Kostromitin – Exploring Death Through Occultism And Art The travelling theory of art Archives The ISFDB is a community effort to catalog works of science fiction, fantasy, and horror Artvee, archive of public domain classical artworks Heavy music artwork Courses and drawing practice Secrets of shading How to think when you draw The Complete Bridgman fantasy art workshop References Paper sizes Diverse body templates for tattoos Portraits of trees Human anatomy for artists A collection of old book illustrations &amp;ldquo;Invention, it must be humbly admitted, does not consist in creating out of void but out of chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolism in art</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/symbolism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/symbolism/</guid>
      <description>The Three Fates by Alexander Rothaug Table of contents Overview and themes Notable artists Overview and themes Symbolism was a literary and visual art movement from the late 19th century of French, Russian and Belgian origins. Literature, myth religion and poetry are it&amp;rsquo;s main sources of inspiration material, with artists drawing from old mythology, medieval poetry and more modern pieces like Les Fleurs du Mal from Charles Baudelaire as inspiration for visual pieces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/research/</guid>
      <description>Where I keep my references for crafting, woodworking, low-tech, permacomputing and low-bandwidth web projects.
Table of contents Small web Woodworking Tools Electronics Drawing Other crafts Small web Local first apps Notes on writing better image alts Notes on permacomputing Solar protocol for solar powered websites Woodworking Reproductions of early furniture Tools A very complete website on billhooks A website with a lot of instructions on how to make things, all kinds of things The museum of other things Electronics How to broadcast to a CRT TV with a raspberry pi Tool to develop and prototype eurorack modules PCB manufacturing website Drawing and illustration tool to find animal references in a specific angle Other crafts Atelier able - ancient pottery reproduction source for lamp parts </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattooing</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tattooing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tattooing/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Terms Tools Supplies Technique Safety Links Terms CYCLE; Refers to the cycle of motion of the motor of the tattoo machine, pushing the needle out and back in the tube. DWELL TIME; How long the needle is staying in the skin during it&amp;#39;s cycle. GIVE (or SPRINGYNESS); The less dwell time a machine has the more springiness or give it has. This is desirable because it reduces the chances of damaging the skin by dragging needles inside the skin while tattooing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make yourself a website</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/make-yourself-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/make-yourself-a-website/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Interesting websites Practical knowledge The same way as I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine living in a space designed and decorated by someone else based off a generic pattern, I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine my words and my work exist solely in the conformist and reductive spaces that are current day social media apps. When making this website I craved the freedom that I felt when I first started interacting and making stuff on the web as a kid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo ideas</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/tattoo-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/tattoo-ideas/</guid>
      <description> Some of my tattoos on my legs I see my skin as my personal grimoire, adding to it as I make discoveries, have revelations, find talismans and artefacts, come up with new sigils and live new experiences. I also keep a list of tattoo ideas and things I&amp;rsquo;d like to add to the grimoire over time.
Ghost reading (inspired by Blashpemous) Magic Square - SATOR AREPO Magic circles Stone circle (around belly button) Skull on hand (by alixe cooper) Sigils over elbows Poe with lantern from zelda Datajack on the neck Goblin neolithic maze symbol Black swirl on elbow Chandelier with ghost hand Tattoos inspired by folklore Swords / daggers Medieval Mace Bronze age artifacts Dragon Dungeon map / floor plan Hand of glory Medieval illustrations henbane and other psychoactive witchy plants on my lower legs Crossbow Lord of the rings inspired tattoos Frame saw Heraldic griffin on my back FOLK LORE on fingers (by Empousai ) Two crossed oak branches on my chest (by Alixe Cooper ) broken halberd on my leg by myself Satanic skull with smoke by myself GRIMOIRE over knee by myself Two little imps with a trans symbol by myself Sun scythe by myself Little mouse with an eye by La Spectre Big flail (by Empousai ) ONLY FREAKS lettering (by Horseforest ) Ghost with flail (by Meagan Blackwood ) Ghost pepper (by Evey lp) Coffee ghost (by Evey lp) Bike gear (by Evey lp) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing and harvesting herbs</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/herbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/herbs/</guid>
      <description>This little guide act as a reminder for our own little balcony garden of fresh herbs so the tips will be tailored for herbs growing in terra cotta pots outside on a balcony.
Herb growing and care Planting Mediteranean woody herbs (lavender, thyme, sage, rosemary, oregano) These prefer a mix of 1/3 sand to 2/3 compost to emulate the drier and sandier sands of the Mediteranean. They also need soil that drains quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wood species</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/wood-species/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/wood-species/</guid>
      <description>First and foremost, the most sustainable form of timber is reclaimed wood. Good sources of reclaimed wood are wooden pallets (commonly built of white oak if the wood is hard or pine if soft), timber from demolition of buildings and barns, old furniture. You can find more information on identifying pallet wood here: Identifying pallet wood .
Notes on sustainably harvested timber: buying European wood is usually a good choice because since 2010, the EU Timber Regulation enforced the replanting of trees, better forest management and limiting annual harvests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasonal produce of Québec</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/seasonal-produce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/seasonal-produce/</guid>
      <description>All year long These are not affected by seasonality Beets
Carrots
Mushrooms
Onions
Cabbage
Leeks
Garlic
Potatoes
Rutabaga
Sweet potatoes
Spring from the end of March to the end of June Apples
Asparagus
Cucumber
Celeriac
Radishes
Rhubarb
Snow peas
Spinach
Tomatoes
Summer from the end of June to the end of September Beans
Blueberries
Broccoli
Celery
Corn
Cucumber
Eggplant
Fennel
Grapes
Green onions
Ground cherries
Kale
Lettuce
Pears
Peas
Radishes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-tech</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/low-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/low-tech/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Examples of low-tech Resources With the ongoing climate crisis, the destruction brought forth by the unsustainable push for constant growth of capitalism and a world filled with increasingly complex and disposable machines and tools, there is very strong need to scale down and simplify our technology and engineering.
Design has become on a lot of ways a self-referential discipline, focussing more and more on aesthetics over creative problem solving or, at the even more basic level, just taking the time to see if there is a problem to solve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-grid living</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/off-grid-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/off-grid-living/</guid>
      <description>This is a very organic gathering of my notes and research on living off-grid, either in a home or in a vehicule (like a boat or a van). I have a dream of building a timber framed house in the woods at some points and to have a van or a boat setup for short-term living so these notes act as preparation, planning and inspiration for those projects.
Table of contents Power Water Fuel Internet Heating Lighting Computers Shower Toilet Insurance Safety Links Power The house and vehicule have quite different power needs, but in a perfect world they would both be powered by renewable energy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant-based proteins</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/proteins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/proteins/</guid>
      <description>Tofu 11g protein per 100g
Apart from being a source of protein it is a good source of iron and calcium. Tofu is pretty neutral and versatile, it is available in silky soft (perfect for desserts) to extra firm (good for meat-like textures). If used in salty meals it&amp;rsquo;s best to marinate it and season it to give it more flavour.
For a better texture, freeze overnight, thaw the day of cooking and press for 15 to 30 minutes before cooking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/research/</guid>
      <description>Where I keep my references for folklore, ancestry and magic research
Table of contents Folklore Ancestry Magic Folklore A website dedicated to the irish bones ancient instrument The collections of the Worcester museum The Met museum Museum of Ireland Gallica - a library of old books, manuscripts and documents The Public domain review Pictures and engravings from old books A blog on medieval woodworking A collection of horror stories in the public domain An archive of old irish documents and photographs An in-depth article about polish painted cottages A great video on wassailing The Spirit Photographs of William Hope A website on the occult sides and folkore of Paris Irish traditionnal music archive The English collections at the Pitt rivers musem London Burial Grounds Special collections of the St-Andrews University Plant lore, legends and lyrics Collection of standing stone photos A website on mudlarking on the shores of the Thames A website on misericord carvings An archive of paintings of megalithic sites Place names in reland The Beast of the Gévaudan Early Celtic art Mythical Ireland Celtic sun worship A Medieval bestiary complete guide to heraldry Website on megaliths of Ireland Ancestry Roots deeper than whiteness Magic and alchemy A very deep website on alchemichal symbolism Ambix, a publication on alchemy The Order of bards, ovates and druids An old pagan network Independent publisher of occult books Hermetic library The Museum of Witchcraft and Magic The internet sacred text archive Putressence, hermal alchemy for death rituals </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sigils and occult symbols</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/sigils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/sigils/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents What are sigils Austin Osman Spare Intuitive Sigils Word Method Rose Cross Method Planetary Square Method My own sigil work Links and References What are sigils A sigil, in it&amp;rsquo;s simplest form is a type of symbol used in a magical or ritual practice. The term sigil derives from the Latin sigillum, meaning &amp;ldquo;seal&amp;rdquo; which becomes clear when looking at the seals in the Key of Solomon for example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyrd terms</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/wyrd-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/wyrd-terms/</guid>
      <description>Here is my ever-growing collection of wyrd terms collected online, in books and in conversations. Getting familiar with these concepts and integrating these words in my vocabulary is part of my commitment to re-enchantment.
ANTHROPODERMIC BIBLIOPEGY; The practice of binding books in human skin. APOTROPAIC; Intended or having powers to ward off evil. ARBORGLYPH; The carving of shapes and symbols in the bark of living trees. TO DITHER; To tremble of shiver with cold (provincialism from Yorkshire).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
