<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dungeon synth on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/dungeon-synth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dungeon synth on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/dungeon-synth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tapes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/tape-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/tape-collection/</guid>
      <description>Just listing all the tapes from my collection here
Table of contents Dark ambient Synth music Metal Dungeon synth Folk Dark ambient The search for the sulphurous well, Tommy Creep Rites of blood and dust, Blood and dust Sun of serpent, moone of cipher, Them Teeth Auditory witchcraft, Them Teeth Alkemisten &amp;amp; vansinnet, Them Teeth Come, deathless, Surachai Hinterpest, Mumbles Synth music Sortilèges, Potochkine Potochkine, Potochkine The devil rides out, Dream division Surlendemain acides, Autmelodi Careful, Boy Harsher Glider 10 reworks, The Sight below ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Synth Show Flyer</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-flyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-flyer/</guid>
      <description>Flyer for an underground show inspired by old-school fantasy visuals.
Flyer for an underground show </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illuminations Album Cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/illuminations/</guid>
      <description>Painting for the cover of the second album &amp;ldquo;Illuminations&amp;rdquo; of the local dungeon synth project Aura Merlin . This second album has more of a new age, melodic ambient vibe with still some solid dungeon synth roots. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for daydreaming or pondering the deep knowledge hidden in old illuminated medieval tomes.
The arwork for it was inspired by medieval manuscripts and the illuminations that embellishes their handwritten pages. I did quite a bit of reasearch on the iconography, the colors and the gilding techniques used back in the day to make something that felt authentic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aura Merlin</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/aura-merlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/aura-merlin/</guid>
      <description>Wizardy dungeon synth logo for Aura Merlin
Aura Merlin logo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Swords Album Cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/aura-merlin-3-swords/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/aura-merlin-3-swords/</guid>
      <description>Painting for the cover of the first album &amp;ldquo;Three Swords&amp;rdquo; of the local dungeon synth project Aura Merlin . The concept for the album was a lonely wanderer making their way to this cave in the woods in a quest to find three magical swords.
&amp;ldquo;Attack, threaten or defend
A gift, three swords, one choice
A passage to transcend
Through a smoky cavern, a voice..&amp;rdquo;
I was inspired by Russian landscape painters from the turn of the century for the colors and ruggedness of the trees in these kinds of snow-covered landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Synth Covers</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-covers/</guid>
      <description>Cassette sleeve designs for fictional dungeon synth albums, I&amp;rsquo;m definitely interested in making real ones so if you have a dungeon synth project and are looking for some cover art contact me!
Silent Gnome - A Contemplative Stroll Through the Castle ruins Mournful Sorcery - A Dark Conjuring of Shadows Depressive Goblin - Into the Deep Caves of Despair </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nihtgengan</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/nihtgengan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/nihtgengan/</guid>
      <description>Hand-drawn band logo for the oniric dungeon synth / darkambient project Nihtgengan
Nihtgengan logo in white on black Nihtgengan logo in black on white </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Howl</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/grimhowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/grimhowl/</guid>
      <description> Grim Howl logo </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
