<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>miniatures on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/miniatures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in miniatures on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/miniatures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Lock</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/vampire-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/vampire-lock/</guid>
      <description>I sculpted this vampiric lock on top of a real steel padlock and kept it functional. The inspiration for it was a drawing I made last year which you can find in my Sketchbook of December 2020 . My intent was to make something that feels old and a bit out of time and slightly threatening, something you think twice before unlocking.
The completed and painted vampiric lock We used this lock in a recent photoshoot for our band Blood and dust .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vambit conversion</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/vambit-conversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/vambit-conversion/</guid>
      <description>The original vambits were a small run of laser cut acrylic toys designed by the folks at Hundred Rabbits , I had it laying around on my desk for years and it always had a missing art and antler. Since it was already a bit damaged it gave me the idea of making it really rough looking while practicing my miniature painting skills at the same time.
The final vambit with its new look </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guillotine model</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/guillotine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/guillotine/</guid>
      <description>I built this model guillotine for fun when I decided to go back to building miniature things, it also was a nice exercice in timber framing since I used real wood joints to assemble the structure. It is built with wood, cardstock and aluminium for the blade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golem Heart dice</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/golem-heart-dice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/golem-heart-dice/</guid>
      <description>Logo for a friend&amp;rsquo;s custom gaming dice project. The lettering is based on an existing font with heavy modifications and texturing. The heart was sculpted in clay, photographed and edited.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interesting in custom gaming dice look up his work here: https://www.instagram.com/golemheartdice/ </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
