<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lizbeth Poirier on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lizbeth Poirier on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/now/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve replaced my now page with a journal, read it here See what I&amp;rsquo;m currently reading , watching , playing .
Desktop altar </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of years</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/end-of-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/end-of-years/</guid>
      <description>This page is a collections of notes, ramblings and highlights for each year I pass through. I&amp;rsquo;m starting this at the end of 2021 with the intention of adding to it yearly. A good companion to this is the Timeline which retraces my projects and notes chronologically.
Highlights of 2022 Started a Patreon with a monthly print club Started tattooing for real Highlights of 2021 Moved in with my partner Hex Published the first issue of Fantômes zine with contributions from a lot of great folks Travelled to Saguenay with some friends Lost my job and found a way better one Started painting again started working on a small dungeon crawler game with Devine started working on a new album for Blood and Dust Made a card game for Treecrets Made black metal logos for 6 bands/projects made a whole lot more black metal logos for fun Got my first big illustration contract which made me consider a path to live from my art Learned a lot more about myself Joined the Stone Club Stayed inside a whole bunch Highlights of 2020 Found my drawing style Released the first Blood and Dust album Turned this website into a more personal website Joined Merveilles again on Mastodon this time </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/watching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/watching/</guid>
      <description>This is my movie watchlist, I keep it yearly, highlight the movies that really stayed with me and keep the movies that really impacted me in the films section .
Still from the opening sequence of the wicker man Table of contents To watch 2022 2021 2020 To watch Delia Derbyshire: The Myths And The Legendary Tapes, Caroline Catz - 2020 Berberian sound studio, Peter Strickland - 2012 Sedmikrásky (Daisies), Věra Chytilová - 1966 The Old Dark House, James Whale - 1932 Wristcutters, Goran Dukic - 2006 The Night of the Demon, Jacques Tourneur - 1957 An Inconvenient Truth, Davis Guggenheim - 2006 L&amp;rsquo;erreur boréale, Richard Desjardins - 1999 Candyman, Nia DaCosta - 2021 Candyman, Bernard Rose - 1992 Antlers, Scott Cooper - 2021 The Cabinet of Doctor Caligari, Robert Wiene - 1920 Metropolis, Fritz Lang - 1927 Throne of Blood, Akira Kurosawa - 1957 Macbeth, Orson Welles - 1948 Andrei Rublev, Andrei Tarkovsky - 1966 The Juniper Tree, Nietzchka Keene - 1990 Tilbury, Viðar Víkingsson - 1987 Picnic at Hanging Rock, Peter Weir - 1975 Requiem for a Village, David Gladwell - 1976 The Lair of the White Worm, Ken Russel - 1988 Solitudo, Pino Borselli - 2008 Border, Ali Abbasi - 2018 Pelican Blood, Karl Golden - 2010 Wake Wood, David Keating - 2009 Dark Waters, Sleepy Hollow, Sam Weiss - 1972 Pastoral: to die in the country, Shūji Terayama - 1974 le diable probablement, Robert Bresson - 1977 The Moon and the Sledgehammer, Philip Trevelyan - 1971 The Void, Jeremy Gillespie, Steven Kostanski - 2017 You won&amp;rsquo;t be alone, Goran Stolevski - 2022 Witchhammer, Otakar Vávra - 1970 The White Reindeer, Erik Blomberg - 1952 Upurga, Ugis Olte - 2022 Godland, Hlynur Pálmason - 2022 Concerning Violence, Göran Olsson - 2014 Fallen Angels 2023 Talk To Me, Danny Philippou &amp;amp; Michael Philippou - 2023 The Virgin Suicides, Sofia Coppola - 1999 BEEF (series), Lee Sung Jin - 2023 For A Fistfull Of Dollars, Sergio Leone - 1964 The Good, the Bad and the Weird, Kim Jee-woon - 2008 Derry Girls (series), Lisa McGee - 2018 Black Mirror (series), Charlie Brooker - 2023 Dungeon and Dragons Honour among thieves, John Francis Daley &amp;amp; Jonathan Goldstein - 2023 Sharp Objects (series), Marti Noxon - 2018 I don&amp;rsquo;t feel at home anymore in this world, Macon Blair - 2017 Come to Daddy, Ant Timpson - 2019 Yellowjackets (series), Ashley Lyle - 2023 Enys Men, Mark Jenkin - 2022 The Ring, Gore Verbinski - 2002 Everybody in the place An Incomplete History of Britain 1984-1992, Jeremy Deller - 2019 Creep, Patrick Brice - 2014 Blair Witch, Adam Wingard - 2016 mushishi, Yuki Urushibara - 2005 Buffy the vampire slayer, Joss Whedon - 1997 Brotherhood of the wolf, Eric Darnell &amp;amp; Tim Johnson - 2001 Paprika, Eric Darnell &amp;amp; Tim Johnson - 2006 Antz, Eric Darnell &amp;amp; Tim Johnson - 1998 Matilda, Danny DeVito - 1996 We&amp;rsquo;re all going to the world&amp;rsquo;s fair, Jane Schoenbrun - 2021 Skinamarink, Kyle Edward Ball - 2022 Nowhere, Gregg Araki - 1997 Princess Mononoke, Hayao Miyazaki - 1997 My neighbour Totoro, Hayao Miyazaki - 1988 2022 Got a better pace of watching movies in 2022, went through an aliens and predator phase and was pleased to see all the good new movies that came out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/reading/</guid>
      <description>The book of english magic, with some artifacts This is my reading list, it contains the books, zines and long form articles I&amp;rsquo;ve read in the past (organized by year) or that I intend to read in the near future.
Table of contents Books Zines Articles and websites Books To read Radical Mycology Peter McCoy Objets low-tech du quotidien Alizée Perrin Then and Now C.S. Lewis If on a Winter&amp;rsquo;s Night a Traveler, Italo Calvino Powers of Darkness: The Lost Version of Dracula, Bram Stoker, Vladimar Asmundsson Psychology and alchemy, C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/playing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/playing/</guid>
      <description>This is the list of games I played or want to play, I keep it yearly and highlight the games that really stayed with me.
Table of contents To play 2022 2021 2020 To play Witchaven Darkest Dungeon Blasphemous Gray Dawn 2022 Harvest Moon Banjo Kazooie Dark Souls Diablo II Starfox 64 2021 Amnesia: the dark descent What remains of Edith Finch 2020 Darkwood Gris </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>My bookmarks of interesting / useful / beautiful websites. I&amp;rsquo;ve also included some links to my topic specific lists of resources at the end of this page. Most of the links on this page were first saved in my local notes on my computer then moved in one of those pages on here.
Castle ruins in Scotland, a reminder that nothing last forever, especially links Table of contents Websites Publications Bookstores Artists Art Tattoo Tattoo Studios Design Politics Spirituality Food Tech &amp;amp; craft Synths Music Tools Events Resources Personal websites and wikis XXIIVV Hundred Rabbits Thomasaurus cblgh Heydon works Tatjana J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On being trans</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/being-trans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/being-trans/</guid>
      <description>I am powerful, fierce, resourceful, creative, weird, caring. I am so much more and also none of that, in my own way. I take some time here to write about womxnhood and encourage everyone to actively challenge how we perceive it. Let the womxn in your life expand your definition of it.
It’s been an incredible journey getting to know the trans womxn I am and coming to terms with how I want to live my life from this point forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Computing Audio Photo and video Computing Apple Macbook Pro 13&amp;quot; mid-2014 with 1TB OWC SSD drive Raspberry Pi 4B+ (I plan to turn it into a resilient computer ) Keychron K6 with green keys Audio Synths Korg Monotron MakeNoise Strega Modular synth Controllers Arturia keystep Arturia beatstep Recorders Tascam DR-40 (Really rugged and the battery lasts a long time, sadly cannot work as an audio interface and the interface isn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive) Audio players Vintage Technics cassette deck Audio Technica record player Headphones Hifiman HE350 (sound quality is good but the open back design can be annoying to others and the cord broke at some point) Photo and video I have often bought photo and video gear for specific projects or to explore new ways of making images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/software/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Visual tools Audio tools Coding tools Utilities Links Software tools for me are mostly a mean to an end, although I do enjoy building them if I have a specific problem and nothing is available that I find simple and efficient enough for the task. I&amp;rsquo;m currently migrating away from proprietary tools towards open source tools compatible with a wider range of OSes and that could run on my resilient computer .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tapes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/tape-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/tape-collection/</guid>
      <description>Just listing all the tapes from my collection here
Table of contents Dark ambient Synth music Metal Dungeon synth Folk Dark ambient The search for the sulphurous well, Tommy Creep Rites of blood and dust, Blood and dust Sun of serpent, moone of cipher, Them Teeth Auditory witchcraft, Them Teeth Alkemisten &amp;amp; vansinnet, Them Teeth Come, deathless, Surachai Hinterpest, Mumbles Synth music Sortilèges, Potochkine Potochkine, Potochkine The devil rides out, Dream division Surlendemain acides, Autmelodi Careful, Boy Harsher Glider 10 reworks, The Sight below ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/talks/</guid>
      <description>Here are the keynote presentations of the talks I have made in the past at design events</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This website</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/this-website/</guid>
      <description>The why This website is part portfolio , part digital garden and part recipe blog . It is where I collect and expand upon my thoughts and discoveries, and where I showcase what I create, craft and conjure.
See the whole structure in the Tree .
Explore projects over time in the Timeline .
Fonts When selecting fonts for this website, I was looking to combine my love for 70&amp;rsquo;s psychedelia and gothic blackletter while keeping everything mostly legible and accessible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo ideas</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/tattoo-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/tattoo-ideas/</guid>
      <description> Some of my tattoos on my legs I see my skin as my personal grimoire, adding to it as I make discoveries, have revelations, find talismans and artefacts, come up with new sigils and live new experiences. I also keep a list of tattoo ideas and things I&amp;rsquo;d like to add to the grimoire over time.
Ghost reading (inspired by Blashpemous) Magic Square - SATOR AREPO Magic circles Stone circle (around belly button) Skull on hand (by alixe cooper) Sigils over elbows Poe with lantern from zelda Datajack on the neck Goblin neolithic maze symbol Black swirl on elbow Chandelier with ghost hand Tattoos inspired by folklore Swords / daggers Medieval Mace Bronze age artifacts Dragon Dungeon map / floor plan Hand of glory Medieval illustrations henbane and other psychoactive witchy plants on my lower legs Crossbow Lord of the rings inspired tattoos Frame saw Heraldic griffin on my back FOLK LORE on fingers (by Empousai ) Two crossed oak branches on my chest (by Alixe Cooper ) broken halberd on my leg by myself Satanic skull with smoke by myself GRIMOIRE over knee by myself Two little imps with a trans symbol by myself Sun scythe by myself Little mouse with an eye by La Spectre Big flail (by Empousai ) ONLY FREAKS lettering (by Horseforest ) Ghost with flail (by Meagan Blackwood ) Ghost pepper (by Evey lp) Coffee ghost (by Evey lp) Bike gear (by Evey lp) </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
