<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Layouts on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Layouts on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Synth Show Flyer</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-flyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-flyer/</guid>
      <description>Flyer for an underground show inspired by old-school fantasy visuals.
Flyer for an underground show </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pious Rot Weapon Compendium</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/weapon-compendium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/weapon-compendium/</guid>
      <description>Together with my friend Steven, we&amp;rsquo;re building a fictional fantasy world called Pious Rot, we started with some of the legendary weapons and their lore and we&amp;rsquo;ll keep going from there. I&amp;rsquo;m putting together these pages for each weapon like if they were part of a full book (hopefully we get to actually make the book one day) with all the stats, the story and the illustrations .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Show Flyer</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-show-flyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-show-flyer/</guid>
      <description>Flyer for an underground noise show in the Mile End of Montreal which we attended as Blood and Dust.
Flyer for a noise show </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of the Repressed Poster</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood-and-dust-poster/</guid>
      <description>Poster design for Blood and Dust , inspired by horror movie posters. The main typography fro the title was done by hand. The photo features Hex .
Poster design for Blood and Dust Detail of the typography Detail of the photo and texture Detail of the bottom details </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-shirt design for Arroliga</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/arroliga-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/arroliga-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>Very metal queer liberation themed t-shirt design for Arroliga .
T-shirt desig for Arroliga </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In This Wet Place</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/orchid-lodge-album-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/orchid-lodge-album-cover/</guid>
      <description>Album cover designed for the latest Orchid Lodge album In This Wet Place , inspired by 80&amp;rsquo;s and 90&amp;rsquo;s 4AD releases.
Orchid Lodge - In This Wet Place album cover I also designed a cassette sleeve variant of this for a short-run self-published tape of the album.
Front of the cassette case and sleeve Back of the cassette case and sleeve Cassette and case Outside of the sleeve Inside of the sleeve with additional text Cassette with pad print </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Synth Covers</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/dungeon-synth-covers/</guid>
      <description>Cassette sleeve designs for fictional dungeon synth albums, I&amp;rsquo;m definitely interested in making real ones so if you have a dungeon synth project and are looking for some cover art contact me!
Silent Gnome - A Contemplative Stroll Through the Castle ruins Mournful Sorcery - A Dark Conjuring of Shadows Depressive Goblin - Into the Deep Caves of Despair </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Around Your Grave I&#39;ll Light a ring of Fire</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/around-your-grave-ill-light-a-ring-of-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/around-your-grave-ill-light-a-ring-of-fire/</guid>
      <description>Cover artwork for a new single by Blood and Dust, listen to it on BandCamp here: https://blood-and-dust.bandcamp.com/track/around-your-grave-ill-light-a-ring-of-fire </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rites of Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/rites-of-blood-and-dust/</guid>
      <description>Album cover and cassette sleeve design for the first Blood and Dust release. The texture used as a background to the design was photographed indoors from soil, leaves and branches collected outside and with the addition of a good amount of fake blood. The concept for this album design, especially the cassette version was to make a physical vessel to contain the music, like an ancient cursed object holding the intense emotions and energy channelled in the songs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood_and_dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/blood_and_dust/</guid>
      <description>Logo and visuals for the ritualistic horror drone project I&amp;rsquo;m doing with Hex. You can find more over on our band website: https://blood-and-dust.com/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrysopoeia typeface</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/chrysopoeia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/chrysopoeia/</guid>
      <description>Chrysopoeia is a custom all-caps typeface I designed in 2017, it&amp;rsquo;s name come from the alchemical process of turning lead and other low metals into gold. All the characters are drawn with lines of a uniform weight, something i was really into at the time. I think there&amp;rsquo;s some interesting ideas in there and I&amp;rsquo;d like to revisit the concept in another typeface one day, going for something closer to the source material, possibly hand-drawn.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
