<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>summer on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/summer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in summer on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chickpea flour omelet</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/chickpea-flour-omelet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/chickpea-flour-omelet/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3/4 cup of chickpea flour 1/2 block of silken tofu 3/4 cup of plant-based milk 1/2 tsp of turmeric salt and pepper to taste olive oil for cooking Steps In a large bowl, mix 3/4 cup of chickpea flour, 1/2 block of silken tofu, 3/4 cup of plant-based milk, 1/2 tsp of turmeric and salt and pepper to taste with a whisk until smooth. Heat up a pan with a little bit of oil in it, when it&amp;rsquo;s hot, pour half of the mix in the pan and cook for 5 minutes or until the bottom side starts to brown, no need to turn it over when it&amp;rsquo;s cooked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marinated veggies</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/pickled-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/pickled-veggies/</guid>
      <description> Ingredients 3 carrots 1 small cucumber 1 jalapeno pepper 1/3 cup apple cider vinegar 1/3 cup rice vinegar 1/2 cup white vinegar 1/2 tsp of sugar 1/2 tsp of salt Steps These are really good in banh mi sandwiches but could also be added to a lot of recipes like bowls or as a side or entrée.
Chop 3 carrots and 1 small cucumber into sticks Cut 1 jalapeno pepper into thin slices, removing the seeds Put the veggies in a mason jar and pour 1/3 cup apple cider vinegar, 1/3 cup rice vinegar and 1/2 cup white vinegar into it, fill the remaining space with cold water to cover the veggies Add 1/2 tsp of sugar and 1/2 tsp of salt and close the lid Put in the fridge overnight </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer chickpea sesame salad</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/summer-sesame-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/summer-sesame-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/4 of a garden cucumber 2 handfuls of mixed salad greens 1/4 of a red onion 1/2 cup of grilled and seasoned chickpeas 2 tsp of plain sesame oil or olive oil 1 tsp of toasted sesame oil 1 tsp of soy sauce 2 tsp of rice vinegar sesame seeds Steps Follow this recipe to make the chickpeas but replace the tofu with chickpeas, I made this salad with leftovers chickpeas from a breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spicy cucumber salad</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/spicy-cucumber-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/spicy-cucumber-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 english cucumber or 3 garden cucumbers 1 tsp of gochugaru 2 garlic cloves 1.5 tbsp of apple cider vinegar 1.5 tbsp of toasted sesame oil 1 tbsp of maple syrup sesame seeds Steps Chop the 2 garlic cloves finely Cut 1 english cucumber or 3 garden cucumbers in medium thick slices In a small bowl combine 1 tsp of gochugaru, the 2 chopped garlic cloves, 1.5 tbsp of apple cider vinegar, 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrambled tofu</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/scrambled-tofu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/scrambled-tofu/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 block firm tofu (strained not pressed) 1/4 cup plant-based milk 1/3 cup nutritional yeast 2 tbsp olive oil 1/2 cup water 3 tsp cumin 2 tsp paprika 2 tsp turmeric 1 tsp garlic powder Salt and pepper to taste Steps In a small bowl combine 1/2 cup of water and 3 tsp cumin, 2 tsp paprika, 2 tsp turmeric and 1 tsp garlic powder. Pour 2 tbsp of oil in a large non stick pan.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
