<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>landscape on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/landscape/</link>
    <description>Recent content in landscape on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/landscape/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The ghost is part of the earth now</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/the-ghost-is-part-of-the-earth-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/the-ghost-is-part-of-the-earth-now/</guid>
      <description>I no more feel like a ghost, i feel like the earth, the soil with it’s deep and complex network of roots and mycelium, with a whole ecosystem of bugs and living things crawling around. I can feel the cover of dead leaves and rotting fruit accumulated on top of me, not hindering my feelings but comforting like a blanket, protecting the bulbs and the nuts that fell on the ground at the turn of the seasons, allowing them to slowly get ready to bloom in the spring, feeding on this bed of decomposing remnants from the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inpathos EP illustrations</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/inpathos-ep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/paintings/inpathos-ep/</guid>
      <description>A series of 4 imaginary landscape paintings for the latest EP of Inpathos called ascension . I focussed on the symbolism of the places I depicted and the feeling they conjure in order to illustrate the different songs.
Painting of shores with high rocky cliffs and blue moonin the distance Painting of the snowy peak of a mountain lost in the clouds Painting of dense woods with a stream going through it, the background fading to fog Painting for the cover of the album, a mountain pass with steep cliffs and some mountains in the distance, a branch crosses the path we&amp;#39;re on and storm clouds are gathering overhead </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failed utopia</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/failed-utopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/failed-utopia/</guid>
      <description>Brutalist ruins of Montreal&amp;rsquo;s olympic stadium and surrounding public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saguenay travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/saguenay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/saguenay/</guid>
      <description>Hiking and climing to see the fjords, riding kids bikes down construction lanes, eating risotto as breakfast, a first escape during the plague.
The fjords of Saguenay Tall cliffs shrouded in fog Grass-roofed cabin Dying little jumping mouse on a bed of moss Mushrooms on log Hex capturing my soul A miniature moss forest in a tiny cave Looming cabins Massive lead and wood religious statue hiding behind trees Cozy spot in the woods Endless roots growing on a boulder Late evening car ride More moss Squatting forest goth Bug-eaten stump Sneaky ferns Shadow-filled woods Towering lookout Jess standing on a boulder Just enjoying the trees The creepiest track marker Empty parking lots Very pastoral traffic cone Suburban wilderness The low tide under the setting sun </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Landscape is Listening</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</guid>
      <description>Walking the urban Landscape of Montreal and noticing it&amp;rsquo;s nature, patterns and textures. Getting lost in the fragmented forest that lives beneath the city.
These photos were taken in the context of the workshop of the same name organized by Lily Hayes &amp;amp; George Saralis-Wheatley, more info can be found here: https://thelandscapeislistening.cargo.site/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun Hell</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/fun_hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/fun_hell/</guid>
      <description>An hommage to the wonderful trash city that is Montréal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</guid>
      <description>Foggy alleys, crumbling buildings and the smell of beer.
Red brick alleyway at night, filled with smoke Back alleys Shawarma is a big thing here Hybrid architecture Alleyway scenes Graffiti on on old painted buildings Antique streetlight in the warm morning glow Halloween night in temple bar The well worn out stools of the local pub Some brutalist architecture Pubs in the morning The beautiful architectural mess that is Dublin A pause in the park Brutalist Dublin airport Palmtrees </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird walking</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/weird-walking/</guid>
      <description>Surreal combination of urban and natural landscape The Weird Walk zine put a name on something I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved to do, wander around cities and nature, following previously unknown paths, keeping my eyes and my mind open for new experiences and noticing weirdness when I encounter it.
I want to keep an irregular log of some of my weird walks here and add notes and references of previous weird walkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban unease</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/suburban-unease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/suburban-unease/</guid>
      <description>A series of cinematic shots of the Montreal suburbs trying to capture the feeling of unease, distrust and inhospitality of higher middle class white neighbourhoods.
Entering a shadowy backyard A mysterious hole in the ground filled with concrete debris Empty windows looming, covered in vine Perfect spot to peak at passerbys through the blinds and the overgrown bushes Windows like empty eyes trapped behind fences The local church Houses built like an overprotective parent with a gaping mouth as a door Little signs letting you that there&amp;#39;s always someone watching Who knows what happens behind closed (garage) doors </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smothered</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/smothered/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/smothered/</guid>
      <description>A heavy white blanket swallowing the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland travel log</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/iceland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/iceland/</guid>
      <description>Barren landscapes, black sand and fish bones. A journey through the harsh Icelandic winter, discovering it&amp;rsquo;s rich cultural and historical past, simple way of life and complex language.
Table of contents The city The nature The flea market The food The statue garden The history The fish drying racks Since music and the arts are running so deep in Icelandic culture (it is said jokingly by the locals that most people are at least in a band), here&amp;rsquo;s some local music to listen to while reading this travel log:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miniature landscapes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/miniature-landscapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/miniature-landscapes/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the miniature landscapes found in nature, microcosms contained into and evoking the larger landscapes that they are part of.
Snow covered cliff with small bushes poking through A patch of long grass amongst the snow Tumultuous waters rushing through boulders Fallen tree in the woods with melting snow Strong waters, freezed in time Sun rays on a frozen lake with a large broken tree in the distance A small clearing with sticks and leaves on a blanket of snow </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
