<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>game on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in game on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playing</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/playing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/playing/</guid>
      <description>This is the list of games I played or want to play, I keep it yearly and highlight the games that really stayed with me.
Table of contents To play 2022 2021 2020 To play Witchaven Darkest Dungeon Blasphemous Gray Dawn 2022 Harvest Moon Banjo Kazooie Dark Souls Diablo II Starfox 64 2021 Amnesia: the dark descent What remains of Edith Finch 2020 Darkwood Gris </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treecrets</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/shop/treecrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/shop/treecrets/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pious Rot Weapon Compendium</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/weapon-compendium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/layouts/weapon-compendium/</guid>
      <description>Together with my friend Steven, we&amp;rsquo;re building a fictional fantasy world called Pious Rot, we started with some of the legendary weapons and their lore and we&amp;rsquo;ll keep going from there. I&amp;rsquo;m putting together these pages for each weapon like if they were part of a full book (hopefully we get to actually make the book one day) with all the stats, the story and the illustrations .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pious Rot Weapon Compendium Illustrations</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/weapon-compendium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/weapon-compendium/</guid>
      <description>In collaboration with my friend Steven, I&amp;rsquo;m illustrating a series of TTRPG weapons from a fantasy world we&amp;rsquo;re creating called Pious Rot. Every weapon has some lore and stats attached to it which informs the illustration I make for it. We&amp;rsquo;re also making these following different parts of the fantasy world and I try to create a sense of local culture and craft between them. We&amp;rsquo;re making a new one every week for the time being until we&amp;rsquo;re done with all the regions of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Travel Log</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/travel-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/travel-log/</guid>
      <description>An illustrated logo inspired by old-school DnD Manuals made for the DnD lore podcast The Travel Log.
Travel log logo on an old tome illustration </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wassail</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/wassail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/wassail/</guid>
      <description>Illustration for a small game made by James Chip inspired by the folk tradition of wassailing.
Cover illustration showing a tree, apples, and a playing card Page frame with trees Small detail illustration showing a ribbon connecting a tree, a mug of hot drink, a playing card and the setting sun </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treecrets cards</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/treecrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/treecrets/</guid>
      <description>Basing myself on a game by James Chip , I created a series of cards with illustrations for the different steps of this meditative and introspective game about listening and talking to trees with your friends.
Treecrets cards Set of 12 cards guiding you and a through this meditative game to be played alone or with a friend in a quiet spot of forest. 20$ CAD
Add to cart </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golem Heart dice</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/golem-heart-dice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/golem-heart-dice/</guid>
      <description>Logo for a friend&amp;rsquo;s custom gaming dice project. The lettering is based on an existing font with heavy modifications and texturing. The heart was sculpted in clay, photographed and edited.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interesting in custom gaming dice look up his work here: https://www.instagram.com/golemheartdice/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursed Object</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/cursed-object/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/cursed-object/</guid>
      <description>Hand-drawn lettering, identity system and publisher seal for a publishing company.
Cursed object logo and sigil Cursed object lettering Cursed object publisher&amp;#39;s seal </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
