<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>photo on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/photo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in photo on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/photo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hardware</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Computing Audio Photo and video Computing Apple Macbook Pro 13&amp;quot; mid-2014 with 1TB OWC SSD drive Raspberry Pi 4B+ (I plan to turn it into a resilient computer ) Keychron K6 with green keys Audio Synths Korg Monotron MakeNoise Strega Modular synth Controllers Arturia keystep Arturia beatstep Recorders Tascam DR-40 (Really rugged and the battery lasts a long time, sadly cannot work as an audio interface and the interface isn&amp;rsquo;t really intuitive) Audio players Vintage Technics cassette deck Audio Technica record player Headphones Hifiman HE350 (sound quality is good but the open back design can be annoying to others and the cord broke at some point) Photo and video I have often bought photo and video gear for specific projects or to explore new ways of making images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traverse the Nightmare Fog</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/traverse-the-nightmare-fog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/traverse-the-nightmare-fog/</guid>
      <description>Thick fog was rising from the ground like in a victorian gothic story.
An old brick school with a row of trees disappearing in the fog Trees vaguely visible in the fog Trees and a pointy roof vaguely visible in the fog Headlights shining on a street drenched in fog Large tree with smaller ones slowly fading in the distance Path in a fog covered park Church visible in the distant fog, with leafless trees in the foreground Tortured tree against a fog backdrop Church steeple with some branches Old church in the fog Large brick school with low rolling fog and a tree in the foreground Fenced area in a park covered in fog </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cemetery Walk Samhain 2022</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-samhain-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-samhain-2022/</guid>
      <description>On the eve of Samhain we ventured out at the end of the day to go visit the ruin of the Calvin Presbyterian Church and it&amp;rsquo;s cemetery in the small rural town of Saint-Anicet in Quebec. The whole place was surprisingly well maintained (compared to how it looked in 2002) and contained a wealth of ancient tombstones.
The church was once part of a settlement comprised of people with French, Irish, and Scottish heritage called Godmanchester Village created in the 1820&amp;rsquo;s which only survived around 30 years and was then abandoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cemetery Walk October 2022</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-oct-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery-walk-oct-2022/</guid>
      <description> A collapsing crypt A mystery bone Leaf-covered steps A mysterious figure walking towards the horizon Me standing in an archway An abandoned spiderweb Mysterious figure amongst the graves The sun shining through the leaves Colors turning in the canopy A lonely wooden cross Hex squatting in the long grass Broken cross on the long grass Hex lying down amongst the forgotten Me enjoying the warm sun Another lonely cross Me with some trees in the background </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/spirit-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/spirit-photography/</guid>
      <description>Ghostly portraits of Hex and Kita in the style of victorian spirit photographs. The ghost effect was made in camera and the daguerreotype feel was achieved in editing. A detailed how-to is available on my patreon .
Family portrait with ghostly Hex Ghostly Hex sitting on a stool Kita holding the hand and putting her hand on Hex&amp;#39;s ghost&amp;#39;s shoulder Ghostly Kita sitting on a chair Kita sitting with her hands crossed and veil on her head Portrait of Kita with some old books Ghostly Kita laying on a table Death creeping with it&amp;#39;s skeleton hand Ghostly Hex squatting Ghostly Kita walking with a candleholder Kita sitting at a table with ghostly Hex Hex as death looking at the camera with their skeletal arm Ghost hand with candleholder Ghost Hex and Kita together Hex sitting on a chair and lighting a match with a ghost passing behind them Ghostly Kita laying down against a stool Hex standing and holding hands with ghostly Kita Hex standing with a double ghostly face </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arroliga</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/arroliga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/lettering/arroliga/</guid>
      <description>Spiky neo-tribal inspired logo for the photographer Arroliga .
Outline version of the logo Full color version </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal artifacts</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/personal-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/personal-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>This ongoing series documents my personal collections of artifacts, some with historical significance, some purely some stick or rock found in the woods somewhere, but all with meaning and a past of future story attached to them. In archeology, artifacts are only as precious as their well-documented provenance and context that allows them to tell a more complete story. These items that I found, unearthed or bought have a story of their own but also a story that I made for them, this is an exercise in collecting those stories so they can be shared and hopefully inspire other people to create stories of their own for their favourite found objects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failed utopia</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/failed-utopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/failed-utopia/</guid>
      <description>Brutalist ruins of Montreal&amp;rsquo;s olympic stadium and surrounding public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saguenay travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/saguenay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/saguenay/</guid>
      <description>Hiking and climing to see the fjords, riding kids bikes down construction lanes, eating risotto as breakfast, a first escape during the plague.
The fjords of Saguenay Tall cliffs shrouded in fog Grass-roofed cabin Dying little jumping mouse on a bed of moss Mushrooms on log Hex capturing my soul A miniature moss forest in a tiny cave Looming cabins Massive lead and wood religious statue hiding behind trees Cozy spot in the woods Endless roots growing on a boulder Late evening car ride More moss Squatting forest goth Bug-eaten stump Sneaky ferns Shadow-filled woods Towering lookout Jess standing on a boulder Just enjoying the trees The creepiest track marker Empty parking lots Very pastoral traffic cone Suburban wilderness The low tide under the setting sun </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Landscape is Listening</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/the_landscape_is_listening/</guid>
      <description>Walking the urban Landscape of Montreal and noticing it&amp;rsquo;s nature, patterns and textures. Getting lost in the fragmented forest that lives beneath the city.
These photos were taken in the context of the workshop of the same name organized by Lily Hayes &amp;amp; George Saralis-Wheatley, more info can be found here: https://thelandscapeislistening.cargo.site/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun Hell</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/fun_hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/fun_hell/</guid>
      <description>An hommage to the wonderful trash city that is Montréal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ominous presence</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/ominous-presence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/ominous-presence/</guid>
      <description>A mysterious haunting figure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellebore zine cover</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/hellebore-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/hellebore-cover/</guid>
      <description>The good folks at Hellebore zine tasked me and Hex to make the cover image for their impromptu Yuletide edition . The theme was the celtic horned god, Cernunnos. With our interpretation of Cernunnos, we wanted to explore the darker aspects of the natural cycle while subverting the gender binary that is often attached to this ancient pagan divinity, channeling Cernunnos within a social and natural context that embraces nuance, complexity, and change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/new-orleans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/new-orleans/</guid>
      <description>Hot sauce, neon lights and plant-covered high balconies.
Tramway tracks and some mighty trees High metal-fenced balconies More beautiful trees Magazine street View from Magazine street Vintage car Frenchman street Those beed necklaces The plants just grow everywhere Architectural details Bubbles and bright colors in the sun Unexpected architecture Voodoo shop Overpass Graffiti culture is alive and well in New Orleans Famous New Orleans Po&amp;#39; Boys Pretty plant Neon signs from inside of a bar </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin travel photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dublin/</guid>
      <description>Foggy alleys, crumbling buildings and the smell of beer.
Red brick alleyway at night, filled with smoke Back alleys Shawarma is a big thing here Hybrid architecture Alleyway scenes Graffiti on on old painted buildings Antique streetlight in the warm morning glow Halloween night in temple bar The well worn out stools of the local pub Some brutalist architecture Pubs in the morning The beautiful architectural mess that is Dublin A pause in the park Brutalist Dublin airport Palmtrees </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodecae</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dodecae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/dodecae/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heavy black veil</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/veil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/veil/</guid>
      <description>Darkness hides what was obvious to better reveal what was occulted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cemetery walk oct 2020</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery_walks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/cemetery_walks/</guid>
      <description>Wandering between worlds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scotland travel log</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/travel-logs/scotland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/travel-logs/scotland/</guid>
      <description>Nature, architecture and haunted places.
The Mountains surrounding the Loch Ness Edinburgh castle from below A dirt path in a field going into a dark forest The ruins of Boleskine House Tapoch Broch Cemetery details Cemetery mushrooms </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban unease</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/suburban-unease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/suburban-unease/</guid>
      <description>A series of cinematic shots of the Montreal suburbs trying to capture the feeling of unease, distrust and inhospitality of higher middle class white neighbourhoods.
Entering a shadowy backyard A mysterious hole in the ground filled with concrete debris Empty windows looming, covered in vine Perfect spot to peak at passerbys through the blinds and the overgrown bushes Windows like empty eyes trapped behind fences The local church Houses built like an overprotective parent with a gaping mouth as a door Little signs letting you that there&amp;#39;s always someone watching Who knows what happens behind closed (garage) doors </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smothered</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/smothered/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/smothered/</guid>
      <description>A heavy white blanket swallowing the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miniature landscapes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/miniature-landscapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/miniature-landscapes/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the miniature landscapes found in nature, microcosms contained into and evoking the larger landscapes that they are part of.
Snow covered cliff with small bushes poking through A patch of long grass amongst the snow Tumultuous waters rushing through boulders Fallen tree in the woods with melting snow Strong waters, freezed in time Sun rays on a frozen lake with a large broken tree in the distance A small clearing with sticks and leaves on a blanket of snow </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
