<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cooking grains and cereals</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/cooking-grains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/cooking-grains/</guid>
      <description>Rolled oats 2 cups of water for every cup of oats.
Combine the oats and water in a pot. Bring to a boil, then reduce to medium heat, let cook for 15 minutes. Steel-cut oats 3 1/2 to 4 cups water for every cup of oats.
Combine the oats and water in a pot. Bring to a boil, then reduce to medium heat, let cook for 20 minutes while stirring from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonbons aux patates</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/bonbons-aux-patates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/bonbons-aux-patates/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 small potato 3 cups powdered sugar 1 tsp of vegan butter 1/2 tsp of vanilla extract 4 tbsp of peanut butter Steps Boil 1 small potato in water until it is soft when poked with a fork, around 15 min Let the potato cool, when it is safe to handle, remove its skin and put in large mixing bowl Add 1 tsp of vegan butter and 1/2 tsp of vanilla extract to the potato and mash very well until there is no more clumps Add 3 cups powdered sugar to the potato mixture in small batches while mixing together, it should create a semi-firm dough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoisin Sauce</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/hoisin-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/hoisin-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/3 cup hoisin sauce 3 tbsp rice vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp hot sauce 2 tbsp sesame oil 1 tbsp ginger 4 cloves of garlic 1 tbsp brown sugar 1 tsp salt black pepper Steps If using apples, cut half an apple in small squares and put in a pan with 1/2 tsp of plant-based butter, cook until sligthly browned. In a small pot combine 1/2 cup of rolled oats and 1 cup of water Cook on medium/high until it boils, around 7 min while stirring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chickpea flour omelet</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/chickpea-flour-omelet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/chickpea-flour-omelet/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3/4 cup of chickpea flour 1/2 block of silken tofu 3/4 cup of plant-based milk 1/2 tsp of turmeric salt and pepper to taste olive oil for cooking Steps In a large bowl, mix 3/4 cup of chickpea flour, 1/2 block of silken tofu, 3/4 cup of plant-based milk, 1/2 tsp of turmeric and salt and pepper to taste with a whisk until smooth. Heat up a pan with a little bit of oil in it, when it&amp;rsquo;s hot, pour half of the mix in the pan and cook for 5 minutes or until the bottom side starts to brown, no need to turn it over when it&amp;rsquo;s cooked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favourite recipes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/favorite-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/favorite-recipes/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Breakfast Sides Pasta Stews Soups Comfort food Sandwiches Desserts Bread Breakfast Vegan buttermilk pancakes Date bread Latkes Sides Kimchi Lembas Grilled brussels sprouts Potato salad Pasta Creamy mushroom pasta Cauliflower mushroom pasta bake Butternut squash pasta Gochujang mushroom pasta Alfredo truffle pasta Tuscan gnocchi Tuna casserole Peanut tofu noodle bowls Mushroom pasta Soba noodles carbonara noodles Stews Southern fried cabbage Japanese curry Spicy vegetable stew Spanish rice with chickpeas Moroccan Tagine Dublin Coddle Soups Zuppa toscana Coconut Curry soup Creamy mushroom ramen Potato and leek soup Broccoli and cheese soup Salads Roasted carrots and chickpea salad Comfort food Lasagna Curry mac and cheese Tofu ribs Cauliflower buffalo wings Spanakopita Wellington Mushroom quesadillas Loaded baked potatoes Cauliflower and butternut squash gratin Mushroom lentil loaf Corn Pone Hard tacos with beyond meat Lentils and mushrooms on mashed potatoes Quiche Fish and chips Mexican rice shepherd&amp;#39;s pie Sandwiches Tempeh Reuben Sandwich Banh mi Jerk wrap Chicken ceasar wrap Desserts Depression cake Cinnamon rolls Brownies Banana bread Fruit cake Tofu chocolate mousse Pumpkin cake Butternut squash pudding Cinnamon rolls Welsh cakes Oatmeal raisin cookies Peanut butter cookies Choco chips cookies Gingersnaps Vegan cheese Cashew camembert Vegan camembert cheese making supplies Sauces Marinara sauce Mushroom ketchup Peanut sauce Alfredo Sauce Dips and butters Vegan nutella Bread Sourdough starter Breakfast sausage bread Borodinski bread </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple crisp oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/apple-crisp-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/apple-crisp-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of rolled oats 1 cup of water 2 tbsp of plant-based milk 2 tbsp of brown sugar half an apple or 2 tbsp of applesauce 1/2 tsp of plant-based butter (if using apples) small handful of granola 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp cloves 1/4 tsp nutmeg Steps If using apples, cut half an apple in small squares and put in a pan with 1/2 tsp of plant-based butter, cook until sligthly browned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish Potato Soup</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/irish-potato-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/irish-potato-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 large potatoes 2 large onions 1/2 cup kale 3 garlic cloves 1 seitan sausage 2 tsp of oil 3 plant-based bacon slices 4 tbsp of vegan butter 2 cups of vegetable broth 4 cups of plant-based milk 1 tsp dried sage 2 tsp dried parsley salt and pepper 1/3 cup vegan parmesan Steps Cut 4 large potatoes and 2 large onions and 3 garlic cloves in thin slices and put them into a large pot along with 4 tbsp of vegan butter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wassail</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/wassail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/wassail/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 large baking apples, peeled and cored 4 cups of ale, beer or cider (alcohol free if desired) 1/2 cup of sugar 1 cinnamon stick, broken in half, or 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1 teaspoon ground ginger zest of 1 lemon Steps Pre-heat your oven to 400°F, cut 3 large baking apples in thick slices and arrange them in a baking dish, sprinkle a bit of sugar on top.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom risotto</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/mushroom-risotto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/mushroom-risotto/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 1/2 cups of arborio rice 2 cups of mushrooms (wild ones are the best) 1/2 cup of vegan parmesan 4 cups of vegetable broth 1.5 cup of light beer 2 tablespoons of vegan butter 3 tsp of fresh thyme a pinch of salt a pinch of pepper green onions or chives Steps Roughly cut the mushrooms in medium sized-chunks Heat up 4 cups of vegetable broth in a pot until simmering, keep at that temperature throughout the cooking process, also keep a cup nearby to transfer the broth Put 1 tablespoon of vegan butter in a pan with the cut mushrooms and cook them slowly until they are slightly browned Put the remaining 1 tablespoon of vegan butter in a large pot and add 1 1/2 cups of arborio rice, roast the rice on high intensity for 2-3 minutes in the butter Lower the burner of the rice to low and start adding the broth to the rice, 1 cup at a time, stirring while the rice cooks and absorbs the broth, then adding more Once all the broth as been absorbed the rice should have doubled in size, it&amp;rsquo;s time to add 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marinated veggies</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/pickled-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/pickled-veggies/</guid>
      <description> Ingredients 3 carrots 1 small cucumber 1 jalapeno pepper 1/3 cup apple cider vinegar 1/3 cup rice vinegar 1/2 cup white vinegar 1/2 tsp of sugar 1/2 tsp of salt Steps These are really good in banh mi sandwiches but could also be added to a lot of recipes like bowls or as a side or entrée.
Chop 3 carrots and 1 small cucumber into sticks Cut 1 jalapeno pepper into thin slices, removing the seeds Put the veggies in a mason jar and pour 1/3 cup apple cider vinegar, 1/3 cup rice vinegar and 1/2 cup white vinegar into it, fill the remaining space with cold water to cover the veggies Add 1/2 tsp of sugar and 1/2 tsp of salt and close the lid Put in the fridge overnight </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer chickpea sesame salad</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/summer-sesame-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/summer-sesame-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/4 of a garden cucumber 2 handfuls of mixed salad greens 1/4 of a red onion 1/2 cup of grilled and seasoned chickpeas 2 tsp of plain sesame oil or olive oil 1 tsp of toasted sesame oil 1 tsp of soy sauce 2 tsp of rice vinegar sesame seeds Steps Follow this recipe to make the chickpeas but replace the tofu with chickpeas, I made this salad with leftovers chickpeas from a breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spicy cucumber salad</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/spicy-cucumber-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/spicy-cucumber-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 english cucumber or 3 garden cucumbers 1 tsp of gochugaru 2 garlic cloves 1.5 tbsp of apple cider vinegar 1.5 tbsp of toasted sesame oil 1 tbsp of maple syrup sesame seeds Steps Chop the 2 garlic cloves finely Cut 1 english cucumber or 3 garden cucumbers in medium thick slices In a small bowl combine 1 tsp of gochugaru, the 2 chopped garlic cloves, 1.5 tbsp of apple cider vinegar, 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing and harvesting herbs</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/herbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/herbs/</guid>
      <description>This little guide act as a reminder for our own little balcony garden of fresh herbs so the tips will be tailored for herbs growing in terra cotta pots outside on a balcony.
Herb growing and care Planting Mediteranean woody herbs (lavender, thyme, sage, rosemary, oregano) These prefer a mix of 1/3 sand to 2/3 compost to emulate the drier and sandier sands of the Mediteranean. They also need soil that drains quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matcha and spirulina latte</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/matcha-spirulina-latte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/matcha-spirulina-latte/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup of plant-based milk 1 tsp of spirulina 2 tsp of matcha powder 1 tbsp of raw sugar (optional) Steps In a small pot combine 1 cup of plant-based milk, 1 tsp of spirulina, 2 tsp of matcha powder and 1 tbsp of raw sugar (if adding it) Cook on medium/high until it starts smoking while continuously whisking it, around 5 min. Turn off the heat and transfer to a mug, enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/winter-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/winter-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats 1 cup of water 2 tbsp of plant-based milk 2 tbsp of brown sugar 2 tbsp of dried cranberries 1/4 tsp of vanilla 6 - 8 entire pecans 1/4 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp cardamom 1/4 tsp cloves 1/4 tsp nutmeg Steps In a small pot combine 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats and 1 cup of water Cook on medium/high until it boils, around 7 min while stirring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasonal produce of Québec</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/seasonal-produce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/seasonal-produce/</guid>
      <description>All year long These are not affected by seasonality Beets
Carrots
Mushrooms
Onions
Cabbage
Leeks
Garlic
Potatoes
Rutabaga
Sweet potatoes
Spring from the end of March to the end of June Apples
Asparagus
Cucumber
Celeriac
Radishes
Rhubarb
Snow peas
Spinach
Tomatoes
Summer from the end of June to the end of September Beans
Blueberries
Broccoli
Celery
Corn
Cucumber
Eggplant
Fennel
Grapes
Green onions
Ground cherries
Kale
Lettuce
Pears
Peas
Radishes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savory miso oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/savory-miso-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/savory-miso-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats 1 cup of water olive oil 1 seitan sausage 1 tsp brown miso 1 tsp soy sauce 1/2 tsp thyme 1 tbsp nutritional yeast 1 green onion Steps cut the seitan sausage in slices and chop the green onion In a pan, put a little olive oil and the sausages slices and cook on medium high until browned, around 5 min At the same time, combine in a small pot 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats and 1 cup of water Cook on medium/high until it boils, around 7 min while stirring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant-based proteins</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/proteins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/proteins/</guid>
      <description>Tofu 11g protein per 100g
Apart from being a source of protein it is a good source of iron and calcium. Tofu is pretty neutral and versatile, it is available in silky soft (perfect for desserts) to extra firm (good for meat-like textures). If used in salty meals it&amp;rsquo;s best to marinate it and season it to give it more flavour.
For a better texture, freeze overnight, thaw the day of cooking and press for 15 to 30 minutes before cooking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poutine</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/poutine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/poutine/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 big potatoes 1 cup of mushrooms 1 onion 1 cup vegetable stock 1 cup plant-based milk 3 tbsp 0f cornstarch 1 tbsp of balsamic vinegar 4 tbsp of olive oil vegan cheese 3 green onions 3 pickles 1/2 tsp nutmeg 1 tsp of smoked paprika 1 tsp of pepper flakes 3 tsp of salt salt pepper Steps Cut the potatoes in 1/2 inch fries-shaped strips, cut the mushrooms in slices, chop the onion in little cubes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrambled tofu</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/scrambled-tofu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/scrambled-tofu/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 block firm tofu (strained not pressed) 1/4 cup plant-based milk 1/3 cup nutritional yeast 2 tbsp olive oil 1/2 cup water 3 tsp cumin 2 tsp paprika 2 tsp turmeric 1 tsp garlic powder Salt and pepper to taste Steps In a small bowl combine 1/2 cup of water and 3 tsp cumin, 2 tsp paprika, 2 tsp turmeric and 1 tsp garlic powder. Pour 2 tbsp of oil in a large non stick pan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall oats</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/food/fall-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/food/fall-oats/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats 1 cup of water 2 tbsp of plant-based milk 2 tbsp of brown sugar pumpkin purée dark chocolate chips pumpkin seeds 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp powdered ginger 1/4 tsp nutmeg Steps In a small pot combine 1/2 cup of steel-cut oats and 1 cup of water Cook on medium/high until it boils, around 7 min while stirring. Turn of the heat and add 2 tbsp of plant-based milk, mix well.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
