<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ghosts on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/ghosts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ghosts on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/ghosts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The ghost is part of the earth now</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/the-ghost-is-part-of-the-earth-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/folklore/the-ghost-is-part-of-the-earth-now/</guid>
      <description>I no more feel like a ghost, i feel like the earth, the soil with it’s deep and complex network of roots and mycelium, with a whole ecosystem of bugs and living things crawling around. I can feel the cover of dead leaves and rotting fruit accumulated on top of me, not hindering my feelings but comforting like a blanket, protecting the bulbs and the nuts that fell on the ground at the turn of the seasons, allowing them to slowly get ready to bloom in the spring, feeding on this bed of decomposing remnants from the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit photography</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/spirit-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/photo/spirit-photography/</guid>
      <description>Ghostly portraits of Hex and Kita in the style of victorian spirit photographs. The ghost effect was made in camera and the daguerreotype feel was achieved in editing. A detailed how-to is available on my patreon .
Family portrait with ghostly Hex Ghostly Hex sitting on a stool Kita holding the hand and putting her hand on Hex&amp;#39;s ghost&amp;#39;s shoulder Ghostly Kita sitting on a chair Kita sitting with her hands crossed and veil on her head Portrait of Kita with some old books Ghostly Kita laying on a table Death creeping with it&amp;#39;s skeleton hand Ghostly Hex squatting Ghostly Kita walking with a candleholder Kita sitting at a table with ghostly Hex Hex as death looking at the camera with their skeletal arm Ghost hand with candleholder Ghost Hex and Kita together Hex sitting on a chair and lighting a match with a ghost passing behind them Ghostly Kita laying down against a stool Hex standing and holding hands with ghostly Kita Hex standing with a double ghostly face </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantômes Zine - issue 1</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/fantomes-zine-issue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/illustration/fantomes-zine-issue-1/</guid>
      <description>Fantômes was my first zine project, one that started very small when I realized that I could regroup in a zine my obsession with ghosts, the drawings I made of them and the photos of ghostly places I took. Then I asked around to see if other people would be interested in creating or writing pieces about ghosts, and got an incredible response. I then spent the next 6 months collecting, assembling, laying out and illustrating all that material to form what became the first issue of this little zine.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
