<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>website on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in website on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This website</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/this-website/</guid>
      <description>The why This website is part portfolio , part digital garden and part recipe blog . It is where I collect and expand upon my thoughts and discoveries, and where I showcase what I create, craft and conjure.
See the whole structure in the Tree .
Explore projects over time in the Timeline .
Fonts When selecting fonts for this website, I was looking to combine my love for 70&amp;rsquo;s psychedelia and gothic blackletter while keeping everything mostly legible and accessible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voidxwitch</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/voidxwitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/voidxwitch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/research/</guid>
      <description>Where I keep my references for crafting, woodworking, low-tech, permacomputing and low-bandwidth web projects.
Table of contents Small web Woodworking Tools Electronics Drawing Other crafts Small web Local first apps Notes on writing better image alts Notes on permacomputing Solar protocol for solar powered websites Woodworking Reproductions of early furniture Tools A very complete website on billhooks A website with a lot of instructions on how to make things, all kinds of things The museum of other things Electronics How to broadcast to a CRT TV with a raspberry pi Tool to develop and prototype eurorack modules PCB manufacturing website Drawing and illustration tool to find animal references in a specific angle Other crafts Atelier able - ancient pottery reproduction source for lamp parts </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make yourself a website</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/make-yourself-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/make-yourself-a-website/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Interesting websites Practical knowledge The same way as I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine living in a space designed and decorated by someone else based off a generic pattern, I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine my words and my work exist solely in the conformist and reductive spaces that are current day social media apps. When making this website I craved the freedom that I felt when I first started interacting and making stuff on the web as a kid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood and Dust</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/blood-and-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/blood-and-dust/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantômes</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/fantomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/websites/fantomes/</guid>
      <description>Small static website for my collaborative ghost story zine Fantômes .
Home page Issue page Ambience page </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
