<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>woodworking on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/woodworking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in woodworking on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/woodworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hammer handle</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/hammer-handle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/hammer-handle/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I found this little ball-peen hammer in an antique store, it had a handle at the time but it ended up breaking with use at the thinner part. The head sat in my tool chest for a couple years until recently when I started to work on my new tool chest project .
With this new motivation to get all my tools together in a new home, I wanted to give this little guy a new handle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tool chest</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tool-chest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/tool-chest/</guid>
      <description>After years of thinking about it and pushing the project back, I finally tackled the building of a proper home for my hand tools. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to use as much of the wood I already have around to make it and the actual structure once was the case containing the first ever modular synth that I put together as a teen.
Since I didn&amp;rsquo;t wanted to draw a full precise plan of it and every tool, here are the guiding principles that I used as I fitted the tools:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coat hanger</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/coat-hanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/coat-hanger/</guid>
      <description>This coat hanger is built in a mix of neo-gothic and eastlake styles out of knotty pine, with moldings and cutout details. The hardware is cast iron and comes from a local company. The whole thing was stained and weathered to look like an antique piece of furniture and hopefully it lives long enough to become one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guillotine model</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/guillotine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/guillotine/</guid>
      <description>I built this model guillotine for fun when I decided to go back to building miniature things, it also was a nice exercice in timber framing since I used real wood joints to assemble the structure. It is built with wood, cardstock and aluminium for the blade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrying mirror</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/scrying-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/scrying-mirror/</guid>
      <description>A mirror to look into the darkest depths. I made this scrying mirror frame out of two pieces of black-painted spruce wood tied together with waxed string - as above, so below. The pieces were carved hollow to hold the mirror without any glue - held safe but still free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Folk magic wands</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/wands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/wands/</guid>
      <description>All of my ritual tools are crafted by hand using hand tools with respect to the tree from which they came from. They are finished with natural linseed oil and wax for durability. After being completed they are cleansed over a flame. Unless specified, they are not created with a specific magical practice in mind and it is up to you to imbue them with your own personal meaning.
I am also open for custom work and commissions, feel free to reach out about those if you’re interested :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox ritual doll</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-fox/</guid>
      <description>The cunning fox escapes the hunter with its prey, crawl underneath brambles to the safety of its lair. Its power lies in its curiosity and ability to see through deceptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death ritual doll</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/craft/ritual-doll-death/</guid>
      <description>With his hollow ribcage, emaciated face and dark tattered robes, he is standing at the crossroads to help souls cross to the other side of the veil. This small ritual doll was crafted during the times leading up to Samhain this year, channeling the transformative energies of the dying season.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
