<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linocut on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/linocut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linocut on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/linocut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>To the otherworld</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/to-the-otherworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/to-the-otherworld/</guid>
      <description>The fifth of my monthly print club
Linocut on paper, 4.5&amp;quot; x 10&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust To the otherworld limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 28, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD
Add to cart </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decay</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/decay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/decay/</guid>
      <description>The forth of my monthly print club, is complementary to the first one, decay and growth working together in an endless cycle, just in time for the coming of death season.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Decay limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 28, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Henbane</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/henbane/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/henbane/</guid>
      <description>The third print of my monthly print club, a henbane plant, one of the psychoactive plants used by witches in their flying ointment.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Henbane limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 24, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hekate</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/hekate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/hekate/</guid>
      <description>Second print of my monthly print club, the key to the underworld and the snake, two symbols of Hekate, the goddess of boundaries, the underworld and witchcraft.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Join the monthly print club on Patreon and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Hekate limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 30, numbered and signed, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/works/print/growth/</guid>
      <description>First print of my monthly print club, a mushroom growing from a hand, a piece about growth and connection with the self and what surrounds us.
Linocut on paper, 3&amp;quot; x 5&amp;quot; - 2022
Become a stone circle patron to join the monthly print club and get an original print by mail every month: https://www.patreon.com/ritualdust Growth limited edition linocut print Small original linocut print, made in an edition of 20, numbered and stamped with my seal, printed on locally made paper 45$ CAD</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
