<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>time on Ritual dust</title>
    <link>https://ritualdust.com/tags/time/</link>
    <description>Recent content in time on Ritual dust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ritualdust.com/tags/time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>End of years</title>
      <link>https://ritualdust.com/about/end-of-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ritualdust.com/about/end-of-years/</guid>
      <description>This page is a collections of notes, ramblings and highlights for each year I pass through. I&amp;rsquo;m starting this at the end of 2021 with the intention of adding to it yearly. A good companion to this is the Timeline which retraces my projects and notes chronologically.
Highlights of 2022 Started a Patreon with a monthly print club Started tattooing for real Highlights of 2021 Moved in with my partner Hex Published the first issue of Fantômes zine with contributions from a lot of great folks Travelled to Saguenay with some friends Lost my job and found a way better one Started painting again started working on a small dungeon crawler game with Devine started working on a new album for Blood and Dust Made a card game for Treecrets Made black metal logos for 6 bands/projects made a whole lot more black metal logos for fun Got my first big illustration contract which made me consider a path to live from my art Learned a lot more about myself Joined the Stone Club Stayed inside a whole bunch Highlights of 2020 Found my drawing style Released the first Blood and Dust album Turned this website into a more personal website Joined Merveilles again on Mastodon this time </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
